<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Bill Wurtz – Questions</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>Unofficial RSS feed for Bill Wurtz questions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>How many owls do you need to see in a short period before you start thinking something is weird?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: How many owls do you need to see in a short period before you start thinking something is weird?

A:
that really depends where you are and where the owls are. there are perfectly normal places to see lots of owls</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you actually like to wear soft clothing (cuz it makes it feel like you're rough in comparison)?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: do you actually like to wear soft clothing (cuz it makes it feel like you're rough in comparison)?

A:
i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if i don't know everything that i dont know but i know that i dont know everything does that mean that i know everything without being smart</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: if i don't know everything that i dont know but i know that i dont know everything does that mean that i know everything without being smart

A:
it's going to give you some philosophical confidence. which can turn out both nice and not nice</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do horses speak to you sometimes?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: do horses speak to you sometimes?

A:
no i dont believe so</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hey! I'm in the process of reinventing the way I write music and I'm curious where you start your writing process. What do you typically start with when writing music?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: hey! I'm in the process of reinventing the way I write music and I'm curious where you start your writing process. What do you typically start with when writing music?

A:
i start with what level of update i want to be working on. For example: if i'm working on update level zero, i'll come up with some brand new things. If i want to be working on things of update level 1, i'll work on only things that i have come up with before but never updated, and update those things. If i'm working on update level 5, then i'll work on only things that have been updated 5 times (well actually 4 times if you dont count the original inception as an update) i should also mention it's quite often that brand new level 0s come at me out of nowhere sometimes when i wasnt even trying to write. those then get added in and become eligible alongside the other level 1s</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>the last line of one of the projects you're working on will contain the letter A.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: the last line of one of the projects you're working on will contain the letter A.

A:
but how much exactly constitutes a 'line'</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How is doubt different from uncertainty</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: How is doubt different from uncertainty

A:
the word 'doubt' probably is more like youre leaning toward 'no' about something. but the word 'uncertainty' is probably less specific. it probably just means you dont know. Which makes me realize i think people probably use 'uncertain' to almost mean 'doubtful' and if you think about it that probably doesnt seem fair, from a linguistic standpoint. but as always there's surely way weirder atrocities just around the next corner, in the lagnuage</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to play the snare drum</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: how to play the snare drum

A:
hit it with a stick, pretty much</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Did u rub your jeans for the percussion of I'm scared?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: Did u rub your jeans for the percussion of I'm scared?

A:
i dont think so, but i know i did it for 'airport terminal'</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What do you think happens inside of black holes?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: What do you think happens inside of black holes?

A:
anything and everything. this is sort of like a book wondering what happens outside the book</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>favorite color gradient?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: favorite color gradient?

A:
how about enjoying a series of slightly different colored gradients, gradually</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why is the math video i uploaded for a class project gaining traction</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: why is the math video i uploaded for a class project gaining traction

A:
maybe it was good</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Are spheres the perfect 3 dimensional objects?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.11.26

Q: Are spheres the perfect 3 dimensional objects?

A:
possibly. as you can see that doesnt mean they are always 'the best', or even any good. well no surely they're good sometimes</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>good golly i feel the urge to create but too fixated on the end product rather than the process. help. i cant be a master of every hobby immediately then i burn myself out. ouchie. how does one conquer this conundrum</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: good golly i feel the urge to create but too fixated on the end product rather than the process. help. i cant be a master of every hobby immediately then i burn myself out. ouchie. how does one conquer this conundrum

A:
it sounds like you have yet to invent yourself into the new king of the avant garde</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Would it be reasonable to call the equals sign ("=") the equator?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: Would it be reasonable to call the equals sign ("=") the equator?

A:
it would be great except in english that word already has a strong universal connotation with the 0 degree latitude line on the earth globe. like even if you were not already talking about globes, youre doing math doing math etc then you say 'equator' and immediately everyone now thinks youre talking about globes. the word is already in use for that. Otherwise it could have been a great word for the equals sign in mathematics, for sure 1.12.26  12:54 am whats your favorite song if any song is any good it ought to be that one, at least while it's on</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>think of the weirdest color you can think of</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: think of the weirdest color you can think of

A:
yellow</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>would you say you like more things than you dislike? or is that impossible to quantify</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: would you say you like more things than you dislike? or is that impossible to quantify

A:
that would be answer B, impossible to quantify. final answer</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>sometimes figuring out the tooling/processes to do something can be fun, but the problem is you can get distracted for a lifetime of improving on it and never actually get shit done. I've been doing this for 2 years at this point and I seem addicted to it despite clearly noticing the problem. How do i stop being an idito</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: sometimes figuring out the tooling/processes to do something can be fun, but the problem is you can get distracted for a lifetime of improving on it and never actually get shit done. I've been doing this for 2 years at this point and I seem addicted to it despite clearly noticing the problem. How do i stop being an idito

A:
it's time to even more honestly weigh the advantages and disadvantages here</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thoughts on E major?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: Thoughts on E major?

A:
higher than Eb major. lower than F major</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is this page called questions and not questions and answers? The answers are a very important part of the experience</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: Why is this page called questions and not questions and answers? The answers are a very important part of the experience

A:
i suppose i didn't want to spoil that part</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thoughts on pitch bending on vibraphone? I like how it sounds like "dee-woo".</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: Thoughts on pitch bending on vibraphone? I like how it sounds like "dee-woo".

A:
so crazy it just might work</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why was 6 afraid of 7?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: Why was 6 afraid of 7?

A:
because they both became so violently trendy so suddenly that corruption and excess drove them into paranoid jealous rage</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What's a prank you like to do</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: What's a prank you like to do

A:
being born</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>are we sure potatoes grow underground? Or do they just hide from humans when they hear us approach?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: are we sure potatoes grow underground? Or do they just hide from humans when they hear us approach?

A:
i don't know that much about potatoes</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is the best kind of clock?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: what is the best kind of clock?

A:
all of them, in due time</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hi bill, i have a physics issue I came up with that i want your opinion on: imagine a perfect sphere one meter in diameter, made of a nondescript matter with perfect curvature and no substructures (atoms, quarks, molecules, etc). A perfect sphere, as if someone just drag-and-dropped a UV sphere from blender into the real world. What do you think would happen when our real atoms touched this theoretical object? would our atoms be pushed into each-other, undergoing fusion, or something more interesting?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: hi bill, i have a physics issue I came up with that i want your opinion on: imagine a perfect sphere one meter in diameter, made of a nondescript matter with perfect curvature and no substructures (atoms, quarks, molecules, etc). A perfect sphere, as if someone just drag-and-dropped a UV sphere from blender into the real world. What do you think would happen when our real atoms touched this theoretical object? would our atoms be pushed into each-other, undergoing fusion, or something more interesting?

A:
according to the description it seems to be monkeying with things on a subatomic level, which, at the very least, means i have no idea what would happen, or if the thing would even be visible, or what. but something tells me there is also something not well enough defined about the question. but i assure you i do not know, i am not a physicist</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Where can I get that red bass from your videos</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: Where can I get that red bass from your videos

A:
i'm still using it, but the good news is it's not special, so you'll be able to accomplish just as much (probably more) with another bass. With the added benefit of, just in case anyone were to notice this, you wouldnt appear to be copying me (which probably no one would notice anyway, because it is a fairly generic looking instrument)</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>any hot tips or sweet tricks on maintaining patience?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: any hot tips or sweet tricks on maintaining patience?

A:
i will tell you them later</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>favorite mathematician?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: favorite mathematician?

A:
euler obviously</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you have perfect pitch? do you wish you did?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.12.26

Q: do you have perfect pitch? do you wish you did?

A:
i would want to know your opinion first, of what you think that means and whether you think it's good</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Would you say you've become quite an expert on answering questions? A real questionnaire you might say?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: Would you say you've become quite an expert on answering questions? A real questionnaire you might say?

A:
'eer' not 'aire', lets say. 'questionaire' already means 'a list of questions'. -eer is more often used for someone who can do something. engineer, racketeer, actually not sure what a racketeer does, make rackets i suppose 1.12.26  8:42 pm any idea how to start making music if I know no music theory nor have any instruments, or how to learn to make music good news, even if you knew how to make music you still wouldnt know</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>where would you go if you could teleport</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: where would you go if you could teleport

A:
anywhere</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I need you to know that the Kiwi has the largest egg to body ratio of any bird on Earth.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: I need you to know that the Kiwi has the largest egg to body ratio of any bird on Earth.

A:
that's very impressive. thanks to you i am very impressed with the Kiwi 1.13.26  4:51 am is the world stupid no</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Favorite time of day?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: Favorite time of day?

A:
</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is it called the kick drum if you don't actually kick it yourself</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: Why is it called the kick drum if you don't actually kick it yourself

A:
close enough, you kick a pedal that kicks it. like when you call someone on the phone, you actually call an operator who calls the person (update! the operater was replaced by a machine! a long time ago actually)</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can you be nostalgic for the present?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: Can you be nostalgic for the present?

A:
yes i believe so. and that's definitely a wonderful trick if you can accomplish it</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how often do your song ideas come from dreams?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: how often do your song ideas come from dreams?

A:
at least a couple times a month</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>If you could invent a new number, what would it be and what would you name it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: If you could invent a new number, what would it be and what would you name it?

A:
let's face it, if i knew what it was then i would have already invented it</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hey bill how is 2026</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: hey bill how is 2026

A:
probably fine, but we MOSTLY dont know yet</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>should i write down songs that I made and played in my head for 2 years before I forget all of them by going through the trouble of garageband</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: should i write down songs that I made and played in my head for 2 years before I forget all of them by going through the trouble of garageband

A:
yes absolutely</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What do you feel are your strengths</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: What do you feel are your strengths

A:
being weak!!!!</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How committed are you to education?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: How committed are you to education?

A:
i'm very serious about educating myself, if that's even possible, and i'm also mindful to educate others when appropriate, BUT that of course can be sand trap of arrogance, because, who am i to assume that i know something that someone else 'doesnt and should' know</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why is socialization so fricking hard and how can i make it easier</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: why is socialization so fricking hard and how can i make it easier

A:
maybe you could find a way to pretend it's..... real</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I know you've gotten music from your dreams before, but have you ever gotten videos?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: I know you've gotten music from your dreams before, but have you ever gotten videos?

A:
yes i believe so</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you think people are born into the world, or born of it, like leaves from a tree?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: do you think people are born into the world, or born of it, like leaves from a tree?

A:
i'm not sure if i understand the difference</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how did you become the person you now are</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: how did you become the person you now are

A:
by being the person i once was</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>bill, i've noticed recently that i have been writing too many songs with descending chord progressions. any idea how i can get myself out of this loop?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: bill, i've noticed recently that i have been writing too many songs with descending chord progressions. any idea how i can get myself out of this loop?

A:
make at least one song without any of these things (whatever they may be), and see what's the most fun you can have doing it</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i find it that you use "meme" as a general term for, among other things, what i would call "meme templates" or even "meme template templates". do you think you have a similar subdistinction</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: i find it that you use "meme" as a general term for, among other things, what i would call "meme templates" or even "meme template templates". do you think you have a similar subdistinction

A:
memes are a meme, that's for sure. and it just so happens that one of the best templates for a meme is in fact the meme template template template template template</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I am the ninth letter of the alphabet.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: I am the ninth letter of the alphabet.

A:
fair play, mate</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>does procrastination imply anticrastination</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: does procrastination imply anticrastination

A:
no i dont believe so</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Should my friend name their dog Bingo?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: Should my friend name their dog Bingo?

A:
that could cause a lot of chaos, but sure</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you sometimes stand in your room?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: Do you sometimes stand in your room?

A:
i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How exactly DOES Believability Bob calculate believability?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: How exactly DOES Believability Bob calculate believability?

A:
believes everything. bob is extremely gullible</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Does our free will to make choices actually create alternate timelines or are we just too busy living in our crazy world to realize we're too predictable to make any other choice?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: Does our free will to make choices actually create alternate timelines or are we just too busy living in our crazy world to realize we're too predictable to make any other choice?

A:
i am certainly a believer in the 'many worlds' theory, of infinitely branching timelines at any given moment, and free will is essentially us choosing which one to go on right now. while i also believe that we will probably do all the others EVENTUALLY as it comes back around in infinite million lifetimes. also i think this necessitates the belief that each one will also be chosen infinite times</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i love your music, would you ever consider making a full length album?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: i love your music, would you ever consider making a full length album?

A:
i always turn out to be more of a song person</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What has been your favorite question asked thus far?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: What has been your favorite question asked thus far?

A:
this one</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>since there is no coloring for "m" in "sumic" on your spotify bio, does that mean your bio on spotify is indeed the word "sumic"</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: since there is no coloring for "m" in "sumic" on your spotify bio, does that mean your bio on spotify is indeed the word "sumic"

A:
yes but that's just music, spelt casually</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>If you had to pay a nickel to listen to nickelback would you want a refund after</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.13.26

Q: If you had to pay a nickel to listen to nickelback would you want a refund after

A:
it's hard to imagine this situation because in general it is free to listen to nickelback</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill, I hope this is not too personal but I remember the time when you didn't feel comfortable sharing your own food consumption preferences (something I find very respectable and reasonable). Can I ask what made you change your mind on the matter? Thanks. Keep up the great work, you are needed.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: Bill, I hope this is not too personal but I remember the time when you didn't feel comfortable sharing your own food consumption preferences (something I find very respectable and reasonable). Can I ask what made you change your mind on the matter? Thanks. Keep up the great work, you are needed.

A:
i've generally found it boring and a little unsettling to talk about physical body processes to a wide audience, HOWEVER, going into the AI era this is changing a little because i think being a real-blooded human-ass being is starting to become a more cherished thing to be proud of. like, i actually use toilets, if you can believe that shit</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you have this question part of your website to entertain fans or for yourself? Does answering them help with the creative process at all by getting your mind "going"?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: Do you have this question part of your website to entertain fans or for yourself? Does answering them help with the creative process at all by getting your mind "going"?

A:
i just love reading things in a purple font</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What are you up to this year? any fun plans?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: What are you up to this year? any fun plans?

A:
i dont plan exactly by year, but i have some ridiculous plans for both the near and distant future 1.14.26  12:39 am what should i do with my life i wouldnt want to spoil the surprise of the different possibilities you'll discover. actually they'd even surprise me because i dont know them</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What's the difference between a connoisseur and an aficionado?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: What's the difference between a connoisseur and an aficionado?

A:
"connaisseur" is from french, meaning expert/judge/taster. "aficionado" is from spanish, it means a fan/enthusiast of something but it also means 'amateur'. The meanings of those 2 words may have merged together a little when used in english, but looking into french and spanish i can see that perhaps the connaisseur may perhaps be a little more high brow than the aficionado</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>any tips on how to reconcile with something you have to live with forever?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: any tips on how to reconcile with something you have to live with forever?

A:
it might be possible to use it to your advantage. ultimately that is the best way to handle these things, if at all possible</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what does your average bass fx chain look like? any tips or warnings for people envious of your mixing?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: what does your average bass fx chain look like? any tips or warnings for people envious of your mixing?

A:
it probably will help a lot to clear the bass frequencies away from the non-bass instruments during times when the full band is playing. single out the instruments that are really doing the low frequency job (bass, kick) and let them have the low end, and keep that mostly out of the other instruments. this can help a lot. and also compressing the bass (not have a lot of loud-soft range) will help usually help. for some reason, wide loud-soft range is usually not too useful on the bass</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I've always felt banjo is a bit of a subpar instrument. I mean, it produces a unique kind of sound so this fact alone justifies its existence, but to me it always lacked some richness and sexiness that comes from other stringed instruments like guitar. (Side note I just realized - banjo is kinda like a reverse bass. Or maybe ukulele is)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: I've always felt banjo is a bit of a subpar instrument. I mean, it produces a unique kind of sound so this fact alone justifies its existence, but to me it always lacked some richness and sexiness that comes from other stringed instruments like guitar. (Side note I just realized - banjo is kinda like a reverse bass. Or maybe ukulele is)

A:
I know it has its use cases and wouldn't want to tell anyone what to play bc who the heck am What are you thoughts on banjo? i've used it in probably the majority of my songs. it's incredibly groovy. so in this case i apologize, if you have ever listened to my music, for all the banjo in it 1.14.26  6:57 am What is your favourite jazz chord hot take there is no such thing as a 'jazz chord' and also a different chord is favored at each moment of the music 1.14.26  6:29 am have you ever thought of making a full length album? yes but i'd rather just make many many many songs</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how many digits of euler's number do you memorize</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: how many digits of euler's number do you memorize

A:
i dont know any of it. havent looked into it yet. i would have but i've been busy making music etc for a long time</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>favorite philosopher?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: favorite philosopher?

A:
surprise me</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you heard of the new instinct-vs-intellect explanation of the human condition and do you think it's probable? basically that our ape ancestors were completely instinctively orientated to love, but that when they developed a conscious mind it clashed with the instincts, causing it to become psychologically upset which is the mad state we still suffer from today and have for eons tried to free ourselves from</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: have you heard of the new instinct-vs-intellect explanation of the human condition and do you think it's probable? basically that our ape ancestors were completely instinctively orientated to love, but that when they developed a conscious mind it clashed with the instincts, causing it to become psychologically upset which is the mad state we still suffer from today and have for eons tried to free ourselves from

A:
i think that's a bit of storytelling and it's certainly not the only way to look at it. another way to look at it (and also not the only way), for example, is: in the past, most animals have had to brutally fight each other for survival in many ways. Nowadays, we humans still find ourselves having to do that to some degree but we are deeply devoted to keeping this at an absolute minimum, we almost unilaterally consider it 'bad', and we are  becoming increasingly more ashamed about it</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what do i say at the interview to make them want to hire me</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: what do i say at the interview to make them want to hire me

A:
one classic trick is to ask them questions</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>can I count on you to live as long as possible.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: can I count on you to live as long as possible.

A:
yes i believe so. i'm very serious about my work, which is intimately connected to being alive</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>sorry if this is a rude question but i suspect you'll answer when the time is right: will people be seeing, hearing and feeling new videos from you soon?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: sorry if this is a rude question but i suspect you'll answer when the time is right: will people be seeing, hearing and feeling new videos from you soon?

A:
yes i believe so</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the sun 5 nanometers away?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: Is the sun 5 nanometers away?

A:
from what, nevermind, no i dont think so 1.14.26  1:25 pm What's your favorite Pokémon? the.... yellow one</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is the best substitute for curtains</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: what is the best substitute for curtains

A:
.... shades?</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do you feel about the word cabbage phonetically? I personally enjoy the sound and texture of it.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: How do you feel about the word cabbage phonetically? I personally enjoy the sound and texture of it.

A:
it's good but not as good as "cribbage"</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you ever think feelings, or feel thoughts?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: do you ever think feelings, or feel thoughts?

A:
now we're talkin 1.14.26  3:35 pm How much time does it typically take for you to respond to a question after it is asked? let's see, donderdag 15 januari 2026 22:27:13 maybe about 31 hours, for example</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is your favorite month and why is it the one you choose?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: What is your favorite month and why is it the one you choose?

A:
whatever month it currently is</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>wat is mgic to u? as in hw u dfine it</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: wat is mgic to u? as in hw u dfine it

A:
magic is a word i sometimes use to describe other things</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i just ate some carrots it was about a 6/10 experience wait i lied it was actually 6.5 it was pretty fun</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: i just ate some carrots it was about a 6/10 experience wait i lied it was actually 6.5 it was pretty fun

A:
i'm following along with the story so far</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>oxford sent me a rejection letter yesterday, should I reject their rejection letter</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: oxford sent me a rejection letter yesterday, should I reject their rejection letter

A:
this could get out of control</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what exact date will you release a new song</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: what exact date will you release a new song

A:
many dates but it will probably be a weekly schedule or something similar</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i actually make music? i like making fun sound on the piano but i look into making music and its just piles of words i dont understand.. so how do you go from "oh this sounds nice" to a completed song?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: how do i actually make music? i like making fun sound on the piano but i look into making music and its just piles of words i dont understand.. so how do you go from "oh this sounds nice" to a completed song?

A:
at some point it's worth asking yourself what you feel a completed song should be. Do you feel other songmakers have gotten it right, or deep down do you wish it was a little different?</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why do we call them cookies if we specifically bake them?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: Why do we call them cookies if we specifically bake them?

A:
some sort of language mixeroo. as usual</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is something that is not a pyramid scheme</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: what is something that is not a pyramid scheme

A:
"fair and square"</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>would you ever not be a princess</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: would you ever not be a princess

A:
i was going to say yes but now that i think about it no</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what if i just made a statement instead of a question</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: what if i just made a statement instead of a question

A:
so crazy it just might work</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Who is going to win the super bowl?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.14.26

Q: Who is going to win the super bowl?

A:
the NFL</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Should I tell my crush that she has the power to break the patterns that torment her?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: Should I tell my crush that she has the power to break the patterns that torment her?

A:
sure but it might be hard to convince her that you also wouldn't mind if she broke those patterns without you</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ive been playing guitar for a while and ive also recently started playing bass. Im still not too good at guitar even after having played it for a year already, and im new to bass so that's obvious how I'm doing. Have you got ANY good tips for continuing my learning of music in general, or anything specific about those instruments?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: Ive been playing guitar for a while and ive also recently started playing bass. Im still not too good at guitar even after having played it for a year already, and im new to bass so that's obvious how I'm doing. Have you got ANY good tips for continuing my learning of music in general, or anything specific about those instruments?

A:
you're going to figure out it all anyway, and it's going to be way more fun than if i tell you the wrong thing at the wrong time</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is your operational definition of "near future"</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: what is your operational definition of "near future"

A:
i suppose it's all relative</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How many Christian communions do you think one would have to attend in order to have consumed one entire Jesus?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: How many Christian communions do you think one would have to attend in order to have consumed one entire Jesus?

A:
sometimes you can get it all in one</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thoughts on anarchy?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: Thoughts on anarchy?

A:
surprisingly organized</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I forgot what I was going to say</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: I forgot what I was going to say

A:
could you tell me? no because you could always change your mind after i predict</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>thoughts on raging bureaucracy?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: thoughts on raging bureaucracy?

A:
seems pretty chill</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you like rain?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: do you like rain?

A:
in moderation</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hello, I just wanted to thank you for something. See, someone I knew recently died of something that almost killed me, and I've been having a horrendous time dealing with all of the things my brain is doing about it. I was feeling exceptionally not OK, went on YT to watch some cat videos to try to calm down, and saw one of your videos in my recommendations. I decided out of curiosity to see which of your videos were released around the time I was sick. And I found out that you posted "if the world doesn't end" right when I was... not quite well yet, but through the dark and experiencing the miracle that I had survived. It helped end a panic attack (so did the cats.) It's so strangely comforting. So I just wanted to thank you. Please keep being weird and amazing. I suppose I need a question here, so... what do you want to do if the world doesn't end?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: Hello, I just wanted to thank you for something. See, someone I knew recently died of something that almost killed me, and I've been having a horrendous time dealing with all of the things my brain is doing about it. I was feeling exceptionally not OK, went on YT to watch some cat videos to try to calm down, and saw one of your videos in my recommendations. I decided out of curiosity to see which of your videos were released around the time I was sick. And I found out that you posted "if the world doesn't end" right when I was... not quite well yet, but through the dark and experiencing the miracle that I had survived. It helped end a panic attack (so did the cats.) It's so strangely comforting. So I just wanted to thank you. Please keep being weird and amazing. I suppose I need a question here, so... what do you want to do if the world doesn't end?

A:
make a huge pile of songs that is twice as high and twice as important as all the others before</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hey I forgot what my last question was what was it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: hey I forgot what my last question was what was it?

A:
was it this</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you have any interesting tales from the creation of the music and/or video of outside?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: Do you have any interesting tales from the creation of the music and/or video of outside?

A:
had the chorus/title idea first</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>the person who said banjo is subpar... what? they've certainly not heard it in the genre, and it can sound quite sad and wistful and profound in the right song. now my question for you: is there an instrument you feel you've underutilised or not used at all but would want to include more?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: the person who said banjo is subpar... what? they've certainly not heard it in the genre, and it can sound quite sad and wistful and profound in the right song. now my question for you: is there an instrument you feel you've underutilised or not used at all but would want to include more?

A:
jeans, for sure</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is the answer to the ultimate question of life, the universe, and everything?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1.15.26

Q: what is the answer to the ultimate question of life, the universe, and everything?

A:
a book quote.... which sometimes even overshadows the book it's from</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>questions</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>None

Q: questions

A:
ue q stions ask a question</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>