<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Bill Wurtz – Questions</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>Unofficial RSS feed for Bill Wurtz questions</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Do you consider yourself to be grateful or thankful and if so do you feel more one than the other?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 12:54 am

Q: Do you consider yourself to be grateful or thankful and if so do you feel more one than the other?

A: it's probably impossible to measure</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why even exist if not being productive? Attentively, the loud part of my brain</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 1:26 am

Q: Why even exist if not being productive? Attentively, the loud part of my brain

A: probably the reason you like being productive is because you discovered, at some point, you enjoy it. so the good news is you are free to enjoy this again</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>favorite type of fractal</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 2:16 am

Q: favorite type of fractal

A: the fractal illustrating the types of fractals</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what are some of your favorite color combos?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 2:40 am

Q: what are some of your favorite color combos?

A: they'll probably all come around eventually</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ok so when a stream has a lot of sediment coming into it and not enough power (lots of water moving fast for whatever reason) to transport it downstream, it deposits it, raising the water level and reshaping its channel--this is aggradation. when a stream has too much power and not enough sediment load to slow it down, it deepens its channel--this is incision. theres a metaphor for life here...stream power represetning passion? sediment load representing self actualization? do you have any thoughts.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 3:27 am

Q: ok so when a stream has a lot of sediment coming into it and not enough power (lots of water moving fast for whatever reason) to transport it downstream, it deposits it, raising the water level and reshaping its channel--this is aggradation. when a stream has too much power and not enough sediment load to slow it down, it deepens its channel--this is incision. theres a metaphor for life here...stream power represetning passion? sediment load representing self actualization? do you have any thoughts.

A: i think it just represents speed</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do I get to Strawberry Fields?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 5:57 am

Q: How do I get to Strawberry Fields?

A: it's on the west side of central park, probably somewhere near john lennon's huge appartment on 72nd street</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is your favourite power of 2</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 8:20 am

Q: what is your favourite power of 2

A: 2</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why did Prince write using numbers?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 8:47 am

Q: why did Prince write using numbers?

A: in case he ever wanted to change the key?</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hey bill, how do i pull myself out of a barren wasteland?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 9:53 am

Q: hey bill, how do i pull myself out of a barren wasteland?

A: start by building something you'd never have time to build if you werent in a barren wasteland</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i play a lot of metal, would it still be a good idea for me to learn traditional grip and switch between them</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 9:56 am

Q: i play a lot of metal, would it still be a good idea for me to learn traditional grip and switch between them

A: it just depends how strong your craving is for it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hi what are your thoughts on soup... For or against?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 11:56 am

Q: hi what are your thoughts on soup... For or against?

A: there's got to be some middle ground</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is the meaning of life without the existence of a sun?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 12:27 pm

Q: What is the meaning of life without the existence of a sun?

A: any words to describe this would have to be in a different language anyway</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is it so cold?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 1:26 pm

Q: Why is it so cold?

A: to compensate for how warm it was another time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how the hell does stevie wonder..... do that?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 1:49 pm

Q: how the hell does stevie wonder..... do that?

A: it's surely the same way flowers grow, which perhaps nobody knows</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>you ever start improvising while jamming and fall into an endless loophole of hating every note you play? do you know some way out?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 3:43 pm

Q: you ever start improvising while jamming and fall into an endless loophole of hating every note you play? do you know some way out?

A: like weather patterns, it comes around naturally. this may seem like a boring answer but it's just more and more true</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What song made you unwrap the tambourine?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 3:49 pm

Q: What song made you unwrap the tambourine?

A: not a song, it was just destiny</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>my dreamcatcher does not work, how will i catch them?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 4:06 pm

Q: my dreamcatcher does not work, how will i catch them?

A: some of them have a catch/repel toggle switch</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is your favorite element of the periodic table?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 4:51 pm

Q: what is your favorite element of the periodic table?

A: 1</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is it possible to uninvent something?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 5:19 pm

Q: Is it possible to uninvent something?

A: i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>got any plans for feb 30</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 5:50 pm

Q: got any plans for feb 30

A: no, thank goodness</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is this question classified as a question or just a jumbled up piece of words made to sound like a coherent sentence so you can eventually read and waste precious time to answer to?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 6:06 pm

Q: is this question classified as a question or just a jumbled up piece of words made to sound like a coherent sentence so you can eventually read and waste precious time to answer to?

A: it is a question about itself</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to out-news the news?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 6:07 pm

Q: how to out-news the news?

A: make something new happen</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>would you rather have unlimited bacon but no games or unlimited games but no games</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 6:25 pm

Q: would you rather have unlimited bacon but no games or unlimited games but no games

A: just to clarify, any possibility of games</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>bill, how do i struggle</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 6:25 pm

Q: bill, how do i struggle

A: impossible. it can't be done</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if you still have strong feelings for someone you only met once 2 months ago, is that real love?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 7:00 pm

Q: if you still have strong feelings for someone you only met once 2 months ago, is that real love?

A: either way, could language even describe how strong it was or wasnt, assuming there was an exact value</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>opinions on today's pop songs?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 7:55 pm

Q: opinions on today's pop songs?

A: they will one day be past pop songs. seems outlandish yes but i've seen it happen</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>thoughts on crocodiles?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 8:00 pm

Q: thoughts on crocodiles?

A: i've heard they can't go around turns very well</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>my friend and i are obsessed with the first two seconds of ground plane. what are those chords?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 8:03 pm

Q: my friend and i are obsessed with the first two seconds of ground plane. what are those chords?

A: ah, this must be what's written in that glowing suitcase, in pulp fiction</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i like your songs</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 9:06 pm

Q: i like your songs

A: my only answer to this is to make more which are not quite what you'd expect but which i think you will still like</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>when you were a kid did you frolick in the fields and imagine stories in your head, also did you look at the sun?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 9:42 pm

Q: when you were a kid did you frolick in the fields and imagine stories in your head, also did you look at the sun?

A: not quite</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to not get distracted on billwurtz.com</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 10:07 pm

Q: how to not get distracted on billwurtz.com

A: you're gonna have to make your own site</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you like green beans potatoes and</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 10:39 pm

Q: Do you like green beans potatoes and

A: this all hinges on what that 3rd thing is</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what's your opinion on subtext (something implied but not directly stated)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.1.26 11:22 pm

Q: what's your opinion on subtext (something implied but not directly stated)

A: it's never guaranteed that everyone would agree on what exactly has been implied</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i used to be so incredibly in love with the art i saw online. it brought me so much joy and happiness to see that it could evoke so much emotion and was one of my biggest motivations to create my own things. but about a year ago, i saw a piece of art that absolutely broke me in the best and worst way possible. it resonated so deeply with me and made me sob 'till my eyes hurt because of how unbearable the feelings i had for it was. and unexpectedly, all that inspiration and joy that art had sparked within me had been so heavy on my mind that it turned into jealousy and envy. i was jealous because i loved it so much that it hurt to know and realize that i can't make something like it, that i just never put in the effort to be like that. i can't fully enjoy the artists i love anymore, because i feel so guilty and shameful for basically hating them for having the will and passion that i lack. i at least kept all that envy to myself and never spoke of it, but i've been hurting deeply inside for so long and everytime i try to make something now i just feel so stupid for even trying. it feels like these hateful thoughts have been eating away at me forever. i don't want that. i really don't want to hate. i don't want to be a hateful person at all. i just want to love. to love everything around me, and myself and what i do. how do i love again?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 12:13 am

Q: i used to be so incredibly in love with the art i saw online. it brought me so much joy and happiness to see that it could evoke so much emotion and was one of my biggest motivations to create my own things. but about a year ago, i saw a piece of art that absolutely broke me in the best and worst way possible. it resonated so deeply with me and made me sob 'till my eyes hurt because of how unbearable the feelings i had for it was. and unexpectedly, all that inspiration and joy that art had sparked within me had been so heavy on my mind that it turned into jealousy and envy. i was jealous because i loved it so much that it hurt to know and realize that i can't make something like it, that i just never put in the effort to be like that. i can't fully enjoy the artists i love anymore, because i feel so guilty and shameful for basically hating them for having the will and passion that i lack. i at least kept all that envy to myself and never spoke of it, but i've been hurting deeply inside for so long and everytime i try to make something now i just feel so stupid for even trying. it feels like these hateful thoughts have been eating away at me forever. i don't want that. i really don't want to hate. i don't want to be a hateful person at all. i just want to love. to love everything around me, and myself and what i do. how do i love again?

A: i dont think i see anything wrong here, you're just finding out how sensitive and intense this game is. your feelings of envy also indicate to me, i think, that you know you're meant to be involved in it somehow. and then also, it's important to remember that this hypnotic superpower you've seen on display is not something that's held under a lock and key somewhere. it flows through all of us, in different ways all the time. actually, what you experienced from that time you saw that thing, that probably says more about you than it does about them. it's at least a 50/50 collaborative moment you had between you and the artist. Perhaps just the other day, that artist maybe saw something by another artist that made them melt with envy. maybe something that would not have moved you in the same way. but then let's say that other artist (the second artist, you being the third, for those keeping score) maybe sees a piece of your work, something youve done, and maybe THAT moves them to tears and sends them into a jealous rage. it all comes full circle, but the knock out 'wow' factor is something that visits us all, it just doesnt like to be told exactly when and where</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i come up witha psuedonym</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 12:19 am

Q: how do i come up witha psuedonym

A: how about bob</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i develop characters that feel like their own unique people with feelings and agency rather than empty vehicles for my ideas?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 1:05 am

Q: how do i develop characters that feel like their own unique people with feelings and agency rather than empty vehicles for my ideas?

A: just like real people, real characters are not for you to develop. they already exist, for real. and as soon as you accept that they are real, the sooner you can get to know them</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you decide when a project is ready to release</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 1:48 am

Q: how do you decide when a project is ready to release

A: if it's EVER..... ANY good</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how many eggs</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 1:54 am

Q: how many eggs

A: gonna need a recount</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how is your imagination in the aphantasia spectrum? Can you imagine an apple and rotate it around and make it purple and stuff or is it more of a phantom view of the general object? (Or is it just not anything at all)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 5:59 am

Q: how is your imagination in the aphantasia spectrum? Can you imagine an apple and rotate it around and make it purple and stuff or is it more of a phantom view of the general object? (Or is it just not anything at all)

A: i can imagine many different configurations of fruit. sometimes can be a good calming down technique, imagining fruit configurations</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What if we pronounced burger like burjer</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 6:28 am

Q: What if we pronounced burger like burjer

A: all it takes is a little courage to try it sometime</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>in the song huge gamer most of the time, how would you type the sound next to "and the levels go in a circle, and around you go..."?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 7:57 am

Q: in the song huge gamer most of the time, how would you type the sound next to "and the levels go in a circle, and around you go..."?

A: [riff]</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>h!, I'm making something now instead of just thinking about it, but I'm stuck for the order in which to do things. There's the singing/producing, the video, and some other writing to do. Do you think it's better to focus on every part (a little bit) every day, or one part (a lot) per day? As in, should Monday be -video day- and so on. I know it'll be different for everyone, but I really wanted to know what you've discovered about this.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 10:12 am

Q: h!, I'm making something now instead of just thinking about it, but I'm stuck for the order in which to do things. There's the singing/producing, the video, and some other writing to do. Do you think it's better to focus on every part (a little bit) every day, or one part (a lot) per day? As in, should Monday be -video day- and so on. I know it'll be different for everyone, but I really wanted to know what you've discovered about this.

A: you could spend a thousand life times trying different ways around this. i'm actually just trying some now</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what should i do if im at the airport terminal and ive heated my porridge for the wrong amount of time?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 12:03 pm

Q: what should i do if im at the airport terminal and ive heated my porridge for the wrong amount of time?

A: you gotta bring it to the multi faith pet relief room</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I always feel like im inherently wrong and sick to my core, and like the very beginning of my bloodline was some sort of disgusting mistake and I really shouldn't exist at all. But I work at an IT help desk and at the end of a work day that feeling always seems to disappear for a little while. My job kind of feels like taking care of babies and even though it's mostly boring it always leaves me feeling like maybe I'm OK even and if that feeling is fleeting I'm glad I have this job</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 12:09 pm

Q: I always feel like im inherently wrong and sick to my core, and like the very beginning of my bloodline was some sort of disgusting mistake and I really shouldn't exist at all. But I work at an IT help desk and at the end of a work day that feeling always seems to disappear for a little while. My job kind of feels like taking care of babies and even though it's mostly boring it always leaves me feeling like maybe I'm OK even and if that feeling is fleeting I'm glad I have this job

A: ah, doing stuff</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do I read more?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 2:55 pm

Q: how do I read more?

A: dare i ask...... do you want to</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>favorite brand of cookie? or other pastry</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 4:31 pm

Q: favorite brand of cookie? or other pastry

A: not a sponsor, but they're very good</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Would you say that playing jazz has influenced your music creation or not?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 4:32 pm

Q: Would you say that playing jazz has influenced your music creation or not?

A: i dont usually like to make those distinctions, under normal circumstances</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>who decided that 6/8 had to be compound. why can't it be 3/4 but faster</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 5:41 pm

Q: who decided that 6/8 had to be compound. why can't it be 3/4 but faster

A: 6/8, according to social norms, is meant to feel like 2/4 with triplets. two beats per bar. that's just what it gets used for</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you ever feel insecure about your appearance and if yes, how do you deal with that feeling?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 7:20 pm

Q: do you ever feel insecure about your appearance and if yes, how do you deal with that feeling?

A: the sooner you can distract yourself with more interesting things.... this can be just enough to get you out of worry mode, which turns out to be what makes all the difference in your appearence as well</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why does English spelling make no sense?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 8:26 pm

Q: Why does English spelling make no sense?

A: i think it's because there's so many things from different origins mixed in. like having a game with a tetris piece, some checkers, some monopoly pieces, some chess pieces, some dice, all mixed into the same game. different rules apply to each piece because it came from a different game</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why is random always random</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 9:09 pm

Q: why is random always random

A: sometimes different things are random than you might think</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you ever fought triangle man?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 9:28 pm

Q: have you ever fought triangle man?

A: not that i recall</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>look directly into the moon</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 9:51 pm

Q: look directly into the moon

A: too bright</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the present moment different from any of the other moments?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 11:08 pm

Q: Is the present moment different from any of the other moments?

A: it has similarities and differences for sure</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>So it turns out it's really easy to spend a lot of time thinking about loads of things you want to do and struggle to decide which one to tackle first. How do you decide which one you want to do first?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.2.26 11:28 pm

Q: So it turns out it's really easy to spend a lot of time thinking about loads of things you want to do and struggle to decide which one to tackle first. How do you decide which one you want to do first?

A: you could spend a thousand life times trying different ways around this. i'm actually just trying some now</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>difference between the south pole and north pole?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 12:07 am

Q: difference between the south pole and north pole?

A: put it this way, you can play nintendo at the south pole</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>are you tired of getting questions that quote something else? if not, do you think you'll ever get tired of them?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 1:14 am

Q: are you tired of getting questions that quote something else? if not, do you think you'll ever get tired of them?

A: each one brings me into a comfortable state of wakefulness</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hey bill, if you had one what was your new years resolution?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 2:04 am

Q: hey bill, if you had one what was your new years resolution?

A: to make resolutions at other parts of the year. wait actually that was also a resolution that i made at a different time of the year</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you have any formal music training or are you self-taught?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 2:22 am

Q: do you have any formal music training or are you self-taught?

A: i would vehemently argue that music itself is not as formal as you think</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm tired and I didn't study for a midterm but now I have to. Should I quit everything and live in a hut in the woods?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 6:38 am

Q: I'm tired and I didn't study for a midterm but now I have to. Should I quit everything and live in a hut in the woods?

A: only if you find a really really good, irresistible hut</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you deal with people/fans expectations? how has that changed since you started doing what you do?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 7:18 am

Q: how do you deal with people/fans expectations? how has that changed since you started doing what you do?

A: it's very motivating, but it also has no influence on me qualitatively</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Would you rhyme eleven with oven</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 7:25 am

Q: Would you rhyme eleven with oven

A: can't predict this any more than you can predict the personality of your child</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why are yawns contagious</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 7:48 am

Q: Why are yawns contagious

A: i'm not sure</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Favourite star? Favourite constellation? Favourite planet? And finally, favourite galaxy?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 8:19 am

Q: Favourite star? Favourite constellation? Favourite planet? And finally, favourite galaxy?

A: i've only been to one, so let's just say this one</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>you get so many questions. how do you have an answer to all of them? how do i learn to know myself enough to answer one?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 9:00 am

Q: you get so many questions. how do you have an answer to all of them? how do i learn to know myself enough to answer one?

A: one easy trick is to skip the ones i really cant answer</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>mnemonics is a nice word</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 9:04 am

Q: mnemonics is a nice word

A: yes but it also seems like it could be a tripping hazard</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How would you play inversions on guitar?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 10:29 am

Q: How would you play inversions on guitar?

A: i see only one much broader issue here which is how to play multiple notes simultaneously on the guitar. but i dont know if there's any answer other than see what your fingers can reach, and what it sounds like</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>can i meet you in september</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 10:46 am

Q: can i meet you in september

A: maybe some other time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Have you built a particle accelerator to accelerate particles?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 10:55 am

Q: Have you built a particle accelerator to accelerate particles?

A: i can just log into one of the existing ones when i need to sort out some particle issues</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is there a perfect combination of words to create the most beautiful message possible?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 11:09 am

Q: is there a perfect combination of words to create the most beautiful message possible?

A: it's different at each moment for each person. also no ceiling to this, so the idea of 'most/best' is out of the question, but if it's working it should certainly feel this way without a doubt</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can you offer me some advice on how to find the courage to release the music I've been working really hard on? I've tried to write music that's authentic to myself (and I really like it) but I'm self conscious that it's actually cringe as hell lmao.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 11:36 am

Q: Can you offer me some advice on how to find the courage to release the music I've been working really hard on? I've tried to write music that's authentic to myself (and I really like it) but I'm self conscious that it's actually cringe as hell lmao.

A: basically just wait to see how miserable you get without releasing it. eventually it should get bad enough that it will be easy motivation</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>are diminished 7 chords even real</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 1:53 pm

Q: are diminished 7 chords even real

A: i think what can happen is, the naming system taught in your textbooks will naturally lead you to a bias that certain namable chords within that system are more common than the ones which dont have names, which is not quite true. BUT, they still very much exist in actual music. at least that one does. (hint: in the key of C, the ones youre most likely to see are the ones like C#dim7, F#dim7, or G#min7. and the next chord will probably be a halfstep higher, such as Dmin7, C/G (C over G bass), or Amin)</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>My job requires me to have creative output during regular 8 hour shifts. How can I possibly wrangle my brain to do the thing when it need to be do</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 2:35 pm

Q: My job requires me to have creative output during regular 8 hour shifts. How can I possibly wrangle my brain to do the thing when it need to be do

A: somehow you'll have to envision a world where you are a co-creator here</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how wide should a highway be</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 3:42 pm

Q: how wide should a highway be

A: at least as wide as the cars</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how are you so good at putting ideas into words?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 3:48 pm

Q: how are you so good at putting ideas into words?

A: stumble around long enough.....</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>can i get a pizza with pineapple</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 3:49 pm

Q: can i get a pizza with pineapple

A: why stop there</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i record vocals? What factors do I have to take more caution to than I initially would've thought? The mic? Acoustics? And then when I'm done, HOW do I mix them?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 4:02 pm

Q: how do i record vocals? What factors do I have to take more caution to than I initially would've thought? The mic? Acoustics? And then when I'm done, HOW do I mix them?

A: youre doing this in the wrong order. do it first, just any way you can, and try to forget about all these questions for as long as you can until the right questions become just so obvious they ask themselves</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do you always seem to know the right thing to say to people on this site? every response of yours that I see on here seems to be funny or insightful in a helpful way.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 4:11 pm

Q: How do you always seem to know the right thing to say to people on this site? every response of yours that I see on here seems to be funny or insightful in a helpful way.

A: ah yes, EXCEPT this one</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When is your next album getting released and how many songs are in it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 4:19 pm

Q: When is your next album getting released and how many songs are in it?

A: i prefer to release songs individually, but i was thinking of doing a billion</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>not all who ask seek answers</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 6:04 pm

Q: not all who ask seek answers

A: to compensate for this, perhaps not all who seek answers ask</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>my whole world just got turned upside down and i don't know what to do with myself. i'm filled with nervous, anxious energy that i want to get rid of but i'm not able to even begin figuring out how. how do i break this cycle?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 6:38 pm

Q: my whole world just got turned upside down and i don't know what to do with myself. i'm filled with nervous, anxious energy that i want to get rid of but i'm not able to even begin figuring out how. how do i break this cycle?

A: sometimes you have to see it as an injury that heals in time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hi bill. do you know how to perform a backstitch after a running stitch? if not do you know how to tie off a running stitch? if neither, i'm sorry</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 7:08 pm

Q: hi bill. do you know how to perform a backstitch after a running stitch? if not do you know how to tie off a running stitch? if neither, i'm sorry

A: i have idea, but you've made this subject seem at least as exciting as skateboarding</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do You Realize That Everyone You Know Someday Will Die??</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 7:10 pm

Q: Do You Realize That Everyone You Know Someday Will Die??

A: thank you for reciting that lyric here</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Where is the wind going?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 7:20 pm

Q: Where is the wind going?

A: over there</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you have goals for 2026 that you didnt have in previous years?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 7:26 pm

Q: do you have goals for 2026 that you didnt have in previous years?

A: i dont make goals 'for a year', because i view those as december/january clickbait</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Just went crazy in a text file, I can see why you recommend this. Thanks</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 7:45 pm

Q: Just went crazy in a text file, I can see why you recommend this. Thanks

A: it may not be for everyone</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you think consciousness is beyond matter, or could you make consciousness with an elaborate enough system of pulleys and levers</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 7:51 pm

Q: do you think consciousness is beyond matter, or could you make consciousness with an elaborate enough system of pulleys and levers

A: the most logical explanation to me seems that it's beyond matter, similar to the way a person playing a musical instrument is not built into the instrument they're just playing the instrument</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i enjoy your content so much that i cant help but say it even if i dont know how to say it in a way that does justice to how much i enjoy your content</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 8:27 pm

Q: i enjoy your content so much that i cant help but say it even if i dont know how to say it in a way that does justice to how much i enjoy your content

A: this is motivating to me of course</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>does creating ever get easier?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 9:21 pm

Q: does creating ever get easier?

A: YES, but then it gets harder then easier and so on</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tigers or lions?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 10:20 pm

Q: Tigers or lions?

A: i can't decide, how about 1 of each</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why do they call it an oven when you of in the food and of out the hot eat the food?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 10:49 pm

Q: why do they call it an oven when you of in the food and of out the hot eat the food?

A: can you not think of a more perfect name</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why do we shiver when we are cold</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 10:54 pm

Q: why do we shiver when we are cold

A: to generate warmth. shaking and movement generates warmth</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you think a song (or really anything) can be perfect? Like, if there was an all knowing all powerful god, could it make a song that would actually feel like perfection to us, or is there a limit to how good music can be.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.3.26 11:04 pm

Q: do you think a song (or really anything) can be perfect? Like, if there was an all knowing all powerful god, could it make a song that would actually feel like perfection to us, or is there a limit to how good music can be.

A: think of it this way: if there were any perfect note it would never cease. the whole reason music exists is because every note or anything you can sing or play is, in some way, wrong. that's why you have to keep switching notes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>thoughts on physical media?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 12:01 am

Q: thoughts on physical media?

A: so crazy it just might work</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I don't want to do anything except eat and sleep. Is something wrong with me?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 12:26 am

Q: I don't want to do anything except eat and sleep. Is something wrong with me?

A: no i dont believe so</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I tried your advice of making the worst possible thing I could in order to get out of creative block. I drew a bunch of penises and swear words and now I just feel kind of confused. Am I doing this wrong? Should I stumble around for longer? Technically it was a penis fractal which made me laugh but that's stupid.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 12:41 am

Q: I tried your advice of making the worst possible thing I could in order to get out of creative block. I drew a bunch of penises and swear words and now I just feel kind of confused. Am I doing this wrong? Should I stumble around for longer? Technically it was a penis fractal which made me laugh but that's stupid.

A: a couple of things i think i'm hearing: 1. you think swear words are bad, you also think penises are bad (despite thinking they are funny) 2. you think laughing is stupid i would say try this: see if you can make it 10 times stupider so you can laugh 10 times harder, then circle back to the question of 'did it work'</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>WHAT ARE CAPITAL LETTERS USED FOR?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 12:44 am

Q: WHAT ARE CAPITAL LETTERS USED FOR?

A: extra clarification in some situations</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you ever caught your reflection staring at you out of the corner of your eye</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 1:08 am

Q: have you ever caught your reflection staring at you out of the corner of your eye

A: i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>This February began on a Sunday, and ends on a Saturday, and is 28 days long. Most calendars show this as a perfect 4x7 rectangle Do you get excited by the cleanliness/satisfaction of phenomena like this? Do you ever get the urge to do something special when confronted when this phenomena? Like making a project centered around a perfectly rectangular 4 week month? I tend to feel this sort of urge</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 4:20 am

Q: This February began on a Sunday, and ends on a Saturday, and is 28 days long. Most calendars show this as a perfect 4x7 rectangle Do you get excited by the cleanliness/satisfaction of phenomena like this? Do you ever get the urge to do something special when confronted when this phenomena? Like making a project centered around a perfectly rectangular 4 week month? I tend to feel this sort of urge

A: sometimes i get inspired to further familiarize myself with the patterns for the whole year(s), etc, and build out the skill of knowing the day of the week for any given date</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>when you think do you dream</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 5:28 am

Q: when you think do you dream

A: to some degree</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I like these lyrics I've made but I feel like they don't go with the instrumental (if you get what I mean). Have you ever gotten into feeling where one day what you wrote you were really happy with and the next you decided it wasn't as good as it felt then? How'd you deal with it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 5:56 am

Q: I like these lyrics I've made but I feel like they don't go with the instrumental (if you get what I mean). Have you ever gotten into feeling where one day what you wrote you were really happy with and the next you decided it wasn't as good as it felt then? How'd you deal with it?

A: after enough years i've realized that this is totally normal. i'm sure i say this often, but just like the same song can work totally differently on 2 different people, it can also work differently to the same person on different days</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you approve of listening to your songs without watching their correspondent video?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 7:06 am

Q: do you approve of listening to your songs without watching their correspondent video?

A: yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why am i so obsessed with e major</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 8:03 am

Q: why am i so obsessed with e major

A: there could be different reasons depending on your instrument</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is your favorite song that you didn't make?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 8:47 am

Q: what is your favorite song that you didn't make?

A: if any song is any good it should feel like the best thing i've ever heard at the time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>name a country in west africa</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 10:01 am

Q: name a country in west africa

A: togo</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the concept that your songs about songwriting a new revelation to you? It seems like it's only been mentioned recently here.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 11:12 am

Q: Is the concept that your songs about songwriting a new revelation to you? It seems like it's only been mentioned recently here.

A: i've known this for many years, but on some level it seems to obvious to me that i sometimes forget to say it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>this semester has been a very busy and hard adjustment, but upon reflection, people told me it would be that way and it's never until i think about it my own way that it starts feeling less hard. would you agree that if something seems impossible, that's all the more reason to try it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 11:36 am

Q: this semester has been a very busy and hard adjustment, but upon reflection, people told me it would be that way and it's never until i think about it my own way that it starts feeling less hard. would you agree that if something seems impossible, that's all the more reason to try it?

A: often a great reason to try things. i can also think of some counterexamples where it might be too unsafe</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What are your personal guidelines to confident decision making?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 11:39 am

Q: What are your personal guidelines to confident decision making?

A: sometimes it helps to know how many chances you're gonna have</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I like making grill cheese sandwiches in my grill cheese sandwich maker, but the store always makes the cheese slices just slightly too big compared to the toast bread, so the cheese always gets everywhere in the grill cheese sandwich maker. How do I fix this</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 11:43 am

Q: I like making grill cheese sandwiches in my grill cheese sandwich maker, but the store always makes the cheese slices just slightly too big compared to the toast bread, so the cheese always gets everywhere in the grill cheese sandwich maker. How do I fix this

A: start a grilled cheese company and build a trusted brand over the course of many generations. the reason i'm saying this is because your story reads just like an origin story for a beloved grilled cheese restaurant of 50+ years</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Have you ever performed the act of worldbuilding, for any reason? If so, can you tell me about it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 12:17 pm

Q: Have you ever performed the act of worldbuilding, for any reason? If so, can you tell me about it?

A: maybe i have without realizing it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>are you real? Am i real? is anything even real?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 12:52 pm

Q: are you real? Am i real? is anything even real?

A: what exactly would it mean not to be</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why is it so hard to find a favorite anything?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 3:13 pm

Q: why is it so hard to find a favorite anything?

A: this probably means the amount of things that are good enough is either more than 1 or less than 1</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>does the day go on?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 3:29 pm

Q: does the day go on?

A: thank you for referencing that song, also the answer is yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you have any advice on uploading content because it feels like nobody cares about what I create</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 3:34 pm

Q: Do you have any advice on uploading content because it feels like nobody cares about what I create

A: ask yourself "what kind would you care about". then it can only be an exciting journey, remedying that situation</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Could you find your way back to earth from 3.5 million lightyears away?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 4:36 pm

Q: Could you find your way back to earth from 3.5 million lightyears away?

A: "back" implies that you came from there, so it's not too unlikely that if you were able to go that far one way, you might be able to make the same journey back</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is bad and what is good?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 5:26 pm

Q: what is bad and what is good?

A: sometimes it's not exactly what you'd expect</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm feeling stressed, both from my own personal battles and from the turmoil on the world stage. Any fun facts to share in these trying times?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 6:31 pm

Q: I'm feeling stressed, both from my own personal battles and from the turmoil on the world stage. Any fun facts to share in these trying times?

A: imagine an outcome where you could look back on this and understand why it made you stronger</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I am suddenly in 10,000 BC surrounded by cavemen and meat. What do I do?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 6:58 pm

Q: I am suddenly in 10,000 BC surrounded by cavemen and meat. What do I do?

A: how about sending a question to me on my website</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>can you give us some perspective on things? thanks, bill</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 7:01 pm

Q: can you give us some perspective on things? thanks, bill

A: sure, i try to do that wherever possible</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>could you please perhaps spare us... a crumb... a snippet... a little screenshot... Of one of the things you're working on... prettybpleaaase just a morsel</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 7:12 pm

Q: could you please perhaps spare us... a crumb... a snippet... a little screenshot... Of one of the things you're working on... prettybpleaaase just a morsel

A: how about the whole thing and then more things</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>steely dan more like steamy ham am i right? how do they sound so,,, "hmmm", "oh yeah..." "hell yeah", "oh yea listen to that... mmmm"</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 7:55 pm

Q: steely dan more like steamy ham am i right? how do they sound so,,, "hmmm", "oh yeah..." "hell yeah", "oh yea listen to that... mmmm"

A: they are into the groundbreaking technique of doing what they wanna do instead of trying to guess what someone else thinks they should do</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how are you so damn creative?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 8:37 pm

Q: how are you so damn creative?

A: it might be just a survival instinct</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i wanna write a song but i really don't know what to do. i play a few instruments but i don't really know where to start. what should i do?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 9:44 pm

Q: i wanna write a song but i really don't know what to do. i play a few instruments but i don't really know where to start. what should i do?

A: there's nothing you 'should' do, but what CAN you do?</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if you were a cat what would your favorite thing to say be</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 10:37 pm

Q: if you were a cat what would your favorite thing to say be

A: meow</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>may i please have a pun</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 10:58 pm

Q: may i please have a pun

A: no whey</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>did you know that the bird is the word?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 10:58 pm

Q: did you know that the bird is the word?

A: there's gonna be a new word, stay tuned</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>in a relative sense (except medically, this could be a science fair) what would be the average cost of some of the pictures located in the gallery for the video "2 friends on a beach?"</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.4.26 11:04 pm

Q: in a relative sense (except medically, this could be a science fair) what would be the average cost of some of the pictures located in the gallery for the video "2 friends on a beach?"

A: [undisclosed]</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do you find the motivation and hope these days?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 12:18 am

Q: How do you find the motivation and hope these days?

A: pretty good</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you put a rabbit into a hat. please help. i need to put my rabbit back into the hat.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 12:45 am

Q: how do you put a rabbit into a hat. please help. i need to put my rabbit back into the hat.

A: the rabbit is already in the hat</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hey Bill, i was one of those guys who asked you stuff about writing. somehow it all worked, and i'm writing better than i ever have. how did you do that?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 1:06 am

Q: hey Bill, i was one of those guys who asked you stuff about writing. somehow it all worked, and i'm writing better than i ever have. how did you do that?

A: i might have been able to give you some good hints based on my experience with it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What makes a interesting question interesting enough to make you interested in the question?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 1:33 am

Q: What makes a interesting question interesting enough to make you interested in the question?

A: if it's written in purple text</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What should be my first action as an evil supervillain?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 2:16 am

Q: What should be my first action as an evil supervillain?

A: how about doing something nice</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you move on from someone without villainizing them?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 2:30 am

Q: how do you move on from someone without villainizing them?

A: the best way around this is to get distracted by someone or something totally different</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what's your favorite horse</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 3:52 am

Q: what's your favorite horse

A: gotta see a list of all the horses so i can think about my selection</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Who would win? 300 000 000 000 000 000 lions or the sun?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 4:06 am

Q: Who would win? 300 000 000 000 000 000 lions or the sun?

A: that's a tie</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Have you ever been to San Francisco</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 4:08 am

Q: Have you ever been to San Francisco

A: i think i have but maybe i've just seen it in the movies</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i stop biting on part of my inner lip</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 5:28 am

Q: how do i stop biting on part of my inner lip

A: you may have to start biting a different part of it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What do birds and bees even have to do with one another</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 7:07 am

Q: What do birds and bees even have to do with one another

A: they're both living on earth at the same time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Best part about music?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 7:59 am

Q: Best part about music?

A: can convey otherwise indescribable feelings, usually unexpectedly</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm an idiot. Advice?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 8:11 am

Q: I'm an idiot. Advice?

A: book tour</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you have any survival tips for someone stuck in a barren wasteland? (asking for a friend)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 9:27 am

Q: Do you have any survival tips for someone stuck in a barren wasteland? (asking for a friend)

A: start by building something you'd never have time to build if you werent in a barren wasteland</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if we don't stand for something, how could we ever stand at all?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 9:34 am

Q: if we don't stand for something, how could we ever stand at all?

A: maybe in this case we need to look elsewhere in the plant and animal kingdom, outside the burden of language, to be reminded why 'standing' in and of itself is a perfectly fine and natural thing to do</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I have a quiz tomorrow. Any idea what the answer to problem two might be?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 9:47 am

Q: I have a quiz tomorrow. Any idea what the answer to problem two might be?

A: i've seen "4" be the answer to the second problem of a quiz before. but you'll have to figure out if that was the same quiz as yours</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Any advice on picking back up fallen/faded dreams?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 10:03 am

Q: Any advice on picking back up fallen/faded dreams?

A: they're probably not nearly as fallen or faded as you think. they could easily be within the normal time frame. like that toaster you bought last week but didnt get around making toast until this week. still works fine, like new</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is your favourite sandwich?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 12:47 pm

Q: What is your favourite sandwich?

A: toast sandwich. for those of you following along at home, this would be one piece of toast between two slices of bread</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you like when people add references to your song titles in their questions? If so then I'm not scared to go on all day doing such :D</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 12:49 pm

Q: Do you like when people add references to your song titles in their questions? If so then I'm not scared to go on all day doing such :D

A: it's not usually something 'added' to a question, it's usually the entire question</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you have the time to listen to me whine about everything and nothing all at once</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 1:07 pm

Q: do you have the time to listen to me whine about everything and nothing all at once

A: thank you for referencing that song here</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>im in my english composition class and its so boring</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 1:14 pm

Q: im in my english composition class and its so boring

A: sometimes boring presentations inspire me to go out and do it better. does this ever happen to you</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I procrastinate a lot. Especially with animating. You got any tips or advice on staying focused?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 1:40 pm

Q: I procrastinate a lot. Especially with animating. You got any tips or advice on staying focused?

A: if this is happening then it means you dont enjoy it enough and it's not easy enough. Think of some of your other hobbies, or stuff you just love to do, cant resist doing it. See if you can spot the differences between your animation routine and these other hobby activities. this will highlight where your animation routine has gone awry</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>If I found myself today, how will I find myself again tomorrow? What if its a different me tomorrow but I really like who I am now. Also, what does it mean to know yourself because I never met anyone like me, yet I like me, today. Can I take now and keep it because its not mine, its shared with tomorrow and yesterday? Do you want to share some of my now? see ya later</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 3:19 pm

Q: If I found myself today, how will I find myself again tomorrow? What if its a different me tomorrow but I really like who I am now. Also, what does it mean to know yourself because I never met anyone like me, yet I like me, today. Can I take now and keep it because its not mine, its shared with tomorrow and yesterday? Do you want to share some of my now? see ya later

A: sounds like the right time to start keeping a journal, of all the different ways you've been</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you think Eminem eats M&amp;Ms?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 3:22 pm

Q: Do you think Eminem eats M&amp;Ms?

A: not implausible</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>the atom is almost entirely empty space. atoms make up us and everything we interact with. how do you feel about this?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 4:08 pm

Q: the atom is almost entirely empty space. atoms make up us and everything we interact with. how do you feel about this?

A: sounds like one of those fun 'wow' factoids. if you make someone go 'wow' then you said it right</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>you ever blink and hear your eyelashes</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 5:29 pm

Q: you ever blink and hear your eyelashes

A: yes in a totally silent room</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What color is science for you, for me it's blue,</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 6:10 pm

Q: What color is science for you, for me it's blue,

A: science can deal with even more than all the colors</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how r u</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 6:48 pm

Q: how r u

A: pretty good</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What do i do if i have too many interests?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 6:53 pm

Q: What do i do if i have too many interests?

A: take a nap</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is the greatest product and why?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 7:08 pm

Q: What is the greatest product and why?

A: 2x2</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what would you say would be a decent start into learning piano [or any instrument]</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 7:44 pm

Q: what would you say would be a decent start into learning piano [or any instrument]

A: find a piano [or any instrument]</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you know if you're cut out for this world</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 7:49 pm

Q: how do you know if you're cut out for this world

A: if you ended up here then you are. that's the whole point. it's like "how to tell if the word 'word' is in this sentence"</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thoughts on limits on "what if" questions. For example "if you could be a car which one. And you have to pick an actual car not 'one that drives fast' "</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 8:00 pm

Q: Thoughts on limits on "what if" questions. For example "if you could be a car which one. And you have to pick an actual car not 'one that drives fast' "

A: the weird thing about these, this one for example, it was their idea for me to be a car. so IF this scenario is happening, it is from THEIR imagination, not mine. so it resembles "what number am i thinking of" but it's written as if it's assumed you should know</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i find myself getting bored with most music (stuff outside of my comfort zone), which is a bummer because most music has a lot to offer. should i try to enjoy most music with a different perspective or just keep listening to the few things i really like?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 8:17 pm

Q: i find myself getting bored with most music (stuff outside of my comfort zone), which is a bummer because most music has a lot to offer. should i try to enjoy most music with a different perspective or just keep listening to the few things i really like?

A: there's something that i think a lot of people dont realize about music....... to fully activate the music experience it needs to be anchored for you somehow. There are plenty of ways this can happen, and it's already happened to you for the music you already like, and you may not even recall what the anchor was for you, but the issue is that there is music out there that has not been anchored for you and youre having trouble finding an in-road. so how do things get anchored? for example: movies can do it. when a song is placed well in a movie, it lifts the movie and it lifts the song to heavenly heights, probably heigher than each could have reached individually. so that's a common way for songs to get their anchor, and then you'll love the song forever after that. Another possible way is if you simply hear it out in public, such as in a retail store or playing out of someone's car. songs can be anchored that way. and as long as you catch what song it was you can add songs to your collection that way, which will always have special meaning to you from the memory of when you heard it that one time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i'm gonna tear my own hair out about what makes an idea worthwhile and what amount of effort satisfies me</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 8:18 pm

Q: i'm gonna tear my own hair out about what makes an idea worthwhile and what amount of effort satisfies me

A: the paradoxical nature of the 'rules' of 'art' are enough for any artist to occasionally risk destroying themselves from their own brainpower</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>does soft clothing implies the existence of angrier clothing? can they also wage a war against each other like music?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 8:21 pm

Q: does soft clothing implies the existence of angrier clothing? can they also wage a war against each other like music?

A: the opposite of angry clothing is, in english, possibly 'nice clothing' which nicely has a double meaning there, possibly more</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ever seen an apparition or floating geometric shape?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 8:57 pm

Q: ever seen an apparition or floating geometric shape?

A: no i dont believe so</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i stop responding to bad things that haven't event happened? Usually its just imagined</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 8:58 pm

Q: how do i stop responding to bad things that haven't event happened? Usually its just imagined

A: it's fairly likely that this will clear up as soon as you give your imagination something else to get busy with</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hi bill. in light of genai and suno and chatgpt and sora i was feeling kinda terrible about the state of art and whatnot but the earnest nature of your music and art brings me hope. thanks. keep up what you do</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 9:05 pm

Q: hi bill. in light of genai and suno and chatgpt and sora i was feeling kinda terrible about the state of art and whatnot but the earnest nature of your music and art brings me hope. thanks. keep up what you do

A: think of it this way, in all the years and decades that we all intellectually bickered and complained that "music is never genuine enough any more", ..... would it not be a huge gift if the value of earnest honesty were to suddenly skyrocket? would that not be a golden age? but then as usual, the golden age is never recognized until later. heck sometimes i'm no good at recognizing it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>recently i've been feeling like i'm always being heard. whenever i think of something that isn't stereotypically "normal" i think about if people around me heard what i thought. then i look at their faces, and i otherthink it. i think that they hear my thoughts. and if they did, they wouldn't like me. i feel so oddly shameful for just thinking thoughts. and they're not even bad thoughts. i just feel like everyone is silently judging me. what is happening???</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 9:05 pm

Q: recently i've been feeling like i'm always being heard. whenever i think of something that isn't stereotypically "normal" i think about if people around me heard what i thought. then i look at their faces, and i otherthink it. i think that they hear my thoughts. and if they did, they wouldn't like me. i feel so oddly shameful for just thinking thoughts. and they're not even bad thoughts. i just feel like everyone is silently judging me. what is happening???

A: you may have underestimated how bored people are of normal thoughts</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i stop pretending my actions dont have significant enough consequences? like, me in my head goes, "oh yeah, seems like a fair trade and I can just take the little bit of a loss" but i know that this cannot be true when dealing with it is just much easier like, damn</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 10:30 pm

Q: how do i stop pretending my actions dont have significant enough consequences? like, me in my head goes, "oh yeah, seems like a fair trade and I can just take the little bit of a loss" but i know that this cannot be true when dealing with it is just much easier like, damn

A: i'm guessing at least some of your transactions go pretty good</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why does it feel like my world has ended? i used to trust people loved me and i used to have so much love for what the world and life could be. i liked daydreaming about projects a lot. even tho i should've done more efforts to make them real they made me feel alive. i was one of the best people in my life. now it feels like my surroundings have dulled. i dont find inspiration or connection with the repetitive cycle of home life and school. im no longer in touch with the old people in my life and i cant connect to anyone anymore. ive tried to find the light in me again but im not sure how i can make a new light if now my circumstances are about being in an environment that makes me anxious and uninspired</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.5.26 11:59 pm

Q: why does it feel like my world has ended? i used to trust people loved me and i used to have so much love for what the world and life could be. i liked daydreaming about projects a lot. even tho i should've done more efforts to make them real they made me feel alive. i was one of the best people in my life. now it feels like my surroundings have dulled. i dont find inspiration or connection with the repetitive cycle of home life and school. im no longer in touch with the old people in my life and i cant connect to anyone anymore. ive tried to find the light in me again but im not sure how i can make a new light if now my circumstances are about being in an environment that makes me anxious and uninspired

A: i want to see an update in two days</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>your favorite season? mine is winter :-)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 12:17 am

Q: your favorite season? mine is winter :-)

A: each one is favoritable, but there's also some inbetween times as well</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do I maintain my spirit when the world seems bent on breaking it? please note, getting my spirit broken would be a big problem for me.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 12:18 am

Q: how do I maintain my spirit when the world seems bent on breaking it? please note, getting my spirit broken would be a big problem for me.

A: sometimes it's worth asking the world if it actually intends to break your spirit</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Shall we amount to something?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 12:30 am

Q: Shall we amount to something?

A: thank you for reciting that quote here</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i think that your music is pretty neat</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 2:25 am

Q: i think that your music is pretty neat

A: [citation needed]</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you subscribe to stoicism, or at least a philosophy that resembles it</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 2:53 am

Q: do you subscribe to stoicism, or at least a philosophy that resembles it

A: not that i know of</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you any recently-released movie recommendations? i've got time and a whole box of microwave popcorn to burn</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 2:53 am

Q: have you any recently-released movie recommendations? i've got time and a whole box of microwave popcorn to burn

A: how about the absolute newest one available to you</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is motivation</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 5:34 am

Q: what is motivation

A: it's the actual reason someone does something</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is information power?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 5:51 am

Q: is information power?

A: sometimes yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you feel alright? Do you remember the days gone by?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 6:31 am

Q: Do you feel alright? Do you remember the days gone by?

A: thank you for referencing that song here</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How many light bulbs does it take to change a person?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 8:00 am

Q: How many light bulbs does it take to change a person?

A: just 1</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Will you be watching the super bowl?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 8:49 am

Q: Will you be watching the super bowl?

A: i'm the ball</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>will there be more after the big batch of videos get released?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 9:19 am

Q: will there be more after the big batch of videos get released?

A: i'll be doing a lot of songs</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have your opinions on bread changed since the 2 or so years ago i have asked this question?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 9:21 am

Q: have your opinions on bread changed since the 2 or so years ago i have asked this question?

A: probably not, but that doesnt mean i cant come up with many different ways to answer that question</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i feel like kind of a failure who's not "doing person" correctly. how do i stop feeling this way when functioning like a "normal person" feels impossible?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 9:31 am

Q: i feel like kind of a failure who's not "doing person" correctly. how do i stop feeling this way when functioning like a "normal person" feels impossible?

A: i'm not sure if you realize how readily people become bored with 'normal'</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>If you could be a baby animal, which one would you pick?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 9:41 am

Q: If you could be a baby animal, which one would you pick?

A: i'm not ready to choose yet</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ever had dinner for breakfast?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 9:55 am

Q: ever had dinner for breakfast?

A: yes i believe so</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Part of how I enjoy art or music is learning about the artist. I like knowing what informed their decisions, what their inspiration was, what kind of person they are, because it all influences their art. A song by you could be thought of as a unique fingerprint only someone with your brain could make. To that end, why don't you ever talk about music you like? You have the right not to, but people ask you and you always avoid giving an answer. Is it because you want your music to stand on its own and don't want people to think about you as a person? Or do you just enjoy the sensation of being an enigma (it does sound fun)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 10:27 am

Q: Part of how I enjoy art or music is learning about the artist. I like knowing what informed their decisions, what their inspiration was, what kind of person they are, because it all influences their art. A song by you could be thought of as a unique fingerprint only someone with your brain could make. To that end, why don't you ever talk about music you like? You have the right not to, but people ask you and you always avoid giving an answer. Is it because you want your music to stand on its own and don't want people to think about you as a person? Or do you just enjoy the sensation of being an enigma (it does sound fun)

A: i'm not sure i understand some of your logic here. i talk deeply about myself as a person, ESPECIALLY about what goes into songwriting, but maybe part of the problem is you have an expectation for me to be someone different than i am</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm writing a film script about a kiosk at the beach. What type of music fits for it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 11:14 am

Q: I'm writing a film script about a kiosk at the beach. What type of music fits for it?

A: this is like another 'what number am i thinking of'. scoring a film without reading it or seeing it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is the huge gamer the rest of the time?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 11:31 am

Q: What is the huge gamer the rest of the time?

A: a lot of people are huge gamers 100% of the time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I have a Spiderman question: So, Spiderman got his powers by getting bit by a radioactive spider. What would happen if I got pit by Spiderman himself? Also, what would happen if Spiderman bit a spider?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 11:39 am

Q: I have a Spiderman question: So, Spiderman got his powers by getting bit by a radioactive spider. What would happen if I got pit by Spiderman himself? Also, what would happen if Spiderman bit a spider?

A: another movie, yay</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is your favorite song (that you made)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 11:45 am

Q: What is your favorite song (that you made)

A: i would prefer to make a new one to be my favorite</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is making music painful to you?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 12:25 pm

Q: Is making music painful to you?

A: it can be sometimes, but that's only to counter balance everything else it does for me</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How are you so creative?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 12:31 pm

Q: How are you so creative?

A: it might be just a survival instinct</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what would you tell your younger self if you could go back 20 years</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 12:56 pm

Q: what would you tell your younger self if you could go back 20 years

A: wouldnt do that; this kind of time-travel communication could create a time paradox, the results of which could cause a chain reaction that would unravel the very fabric of the spacetime continuum and destroy the entire universe</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I can't think of any ueqstions, could you help me?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 1:19 pm

Q: I can't think of any ueqstions, could you help me?

A: just ask the same question as someone else</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>You ever just blast Beethoven's ninth and melt into a puddle of warm jelly?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 2:25 pm

Q: You ever just blast Beethoven's ninth and melt into a puddle of warm jelly?

A: i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how'd you learn music theory? theres some really fun modal stuff in your music</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 2:26 pm

Q: how'd you learn music theory? theres some really fun modal stuff in your music

A: ultimately the way to learn music is the same way to learn speaking or walking, which i also cant explain. it's something that just happens with exposure and experience. also, once you learn walking or speaking, the more terms like "walking theory" or "speaking theory" start to sound silly</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I think your songs have always been about songwriting. The song song is one of your oldest released songs, and its theme is mostly the struggles thou face with songwriting.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 2:53 pm

Q: I think your songs have always been about songwriting. The song song is one of your oldest released songs, and its theme is mostly the struggles thou face with songwriting.

A: that is true</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is 0 an odd or an even number?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 4:27 pm

Q: Is 0 an odd or an even number?

A: i can think of a great argument for it to be even, less of an argument for it to be odd, and a vague feeling that someone might claim it's neither</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what do you think would change about yourself if you became a vampire</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 5:37 pm

Q: what do you think would change about yourself if you became a vampire

A: i dont know anything about vampires</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Correct me if I'm wrong, but you seem to espouse the notion that there are no wrong answers to music. But what about Kid Rock?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 5:51 pm

Q: Correct me if I'm wrong, but you seem to espouse the notion that there are no wrong answers to music. But what about Kid Rock?

A: i dont really know what 'espouse' means, but music is fueled by all kinds of tiny wrongs all over the place. the wrongs are integral to how 'good' it is</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>on a scale of -100 to 13681 how random do you prefer your randomness to be served? (Asking for a friend)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 6:27 pm

Q: on a scale of -100 to 13681 how random do you prefer your randomness to be served? (Asking for a friend)

A: -100</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>If a woodchuck could chuck wood, and I could chuck wood at the woodchuck's wood, what should I do with my fantasy football team in the next game week?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 6:42 pm

Q: If a woodchuck could chuck wood, and I could chuck wood at the woodchuck's wood, what should I do with my fantasy football team in the next game week?

A: get a woodchuck mascot</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hey, bill. i've been writing stories for Years but i've never been able to figure out how any of them should end. do you have any advice?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 6:53 pm

Q: hey, bill. i've been writing stories for Years but i've never been able to figure out how any of them should end. do you have any advice?

A: just start trying things. take a story, try 10 different endings. try 100 different endings. if all else fails then the story will just have to continue</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i sleep</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 7:20 pm

Q: how do i sleep

A: basically you have to get tired of doing everything else</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What do you do when you're not making music?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 7:28 pm

Q: What do you do when you're not making music?

A: make video to go with the music, or make video for music to go with</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you feel about power rangers?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 9:34 pm

Q: how do you feel about power rangers?

A: seems like they made the merchandise first, then the show</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>My parents are gifting me a 70+ year old, fully functioning upright piano, but space in my apartment is limited. Suggestions for how to make it fit?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.6.26 10:17 pm

Q: My parents are gifting me a 70+ year old, fully functioning upright piano, but space in my apartment is limited. Suggestions for how to make it fit?

A: how about a bunk bed with no bottom bed, piano instead</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you like theater at all?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 1:19 am

Q: Do you like theater at all?

A: i like the architecture and the way it can be used performatively, especially putting things on the stage for people to all watch together</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do you build a chord prog on top of an existing melody?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 3:08 am

Q: How do you build a chord prog on top of an existing melody?

A: if youve never done this before, start by just adding one harmony note to just one of the melody notes, at one place in the song. pretend that's all youre allowed to do, and see what you can make of that</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is the name of the character in Im a princess?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 3:15 am

Q: what is the name of the character in Im a princess?

A: it could be you</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is the best songwriting tip you could give me?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 3:46 am

Q: What is the best songwriting tip you could give me?

A: first i need to get a better idea of how it's going so far. for example, giving you an important tip that you've already known since the beginning would not be the best tip</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what's the technique of going ham on a text document about?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 4:22 am

Q: what's the technique of going ham on a text document about?

A: start trying to explore the boundaries of what you actually can and cannot type there</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you understand yourself so well</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 7:25 am

Q: how do you understand yourself so well

A: am slef</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how much are the plane tickets to the land of the 2 letter words</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 7:56 am

Q: how much are the plane tickets to the land of the 2 letter words

A: it depends how far in advance you book</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>any insights on how you think about drum/perc sounds in your songs ? they sound nothing like anything ive heard elsewhere , any influences for your song writting and production? also is stella your favourite jazz standard?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 8:29 am

Q: any insights on how you think about drum/perc sounds in your songs ? they sound nothing like anything ive heard elsewhere , any influences for your song writting and production? also is stella your favourite jazz standard?

A: any insights on how you think about drum/perc sounds in your songs ? they sound nothing like anything ive heard elsewhere , any influences for your song writting and production? usually in music when you start to 'think' it all gets really lame immediately also is stella your favourite jazz standard? i dont believe so</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What's an instrument you've never used before but want to at some point?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 1:25 pm

Q: What's an instrument you've never used before but want to at some point?

A: MEASURED JUDGEMENT</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is music music to your ears?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 2:01 pm

Q: Is music music to your ears?

A: i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how the heck are you so gosh darn wacky</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 3:29 pm

Q: how the heck are you so gosh darn wacky

A: that's just normal. i am normal</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why is the moon associated with night time if it also appears in the daytime</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 4:20 pm

Q: why is the moon associated with night time if it also appears in the daytime

A: because it's generally much more visible at night, and the sun is not</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i hate school and all i want to do are videos</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 4:22 pm

Q: i hate school and all i want to do are videos

A: this will be great news for your videos</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Could you give me a quote to quote?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 4:32 pm

Q: Could you give me a quote to quote?

A: "someone else said this, in some other context"</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is your favorite season? what is one thing that you dont like about that season?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 4:44 pm

Q: what is your favorite season? what is one thing that you dont like about that season?

A: what is your favorite season? the new one what is one thing that you dont like about that season? reminds me that time has elapsed irreversibly</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>can you tell me what it's like to have as many ideas / passions as you? i am lacking severely in both and it's saddening.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 6:39 pm

Q: can you tell me what it's like to have as many ideas / passions as you? i am lacking severely in both and it's saddening.

A: on the flipside it can be overwhelming, confusing, and frustrating to have too many and feel like they all fight with each other and confuse each other</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if adding potassium to water makes it explode, and my body is ~%70 water, will i explode when i eat a banana</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 7:25 pm

Q: if adding potassium to water makes it explode, and my body is ~%70 water, will i explode when i eat a banana

A: no i dont believe so</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>genuine question, how do you typically write music (as in lyrics)? you're writing style is very unique and i genuinely want to know how you are able to articulate an idea into the way you write.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 7:39 pm

Q: genuine question, how do you typically write music (as in lyrics)? you're writing style is very unique and i genuinely want to know how you are able to articulate an idea into the way you write.

A: you say "music (as in lyrics)", this would be the first hazard..... to think of the lyrics separately from the music or melody. Equally problematic is to let the melody writing get too far ahead of the lyrics. The most genuine and healthy songwriting occurs when the words and melody are already attached to each other from the moment of inception. because, often, they rely on each other to justify each other's existence. they justify each other's every turn. that being said, how do these things come to mind? it's like waiting for santa claus except imagine if you had no idea what day or time he was going to show up. also imagine the one thing santa claus hates is to show up exactly when you thought he was supposed to. as a songwriter, the only time things actually work is when you are totally helpless, then it suddenly becomes effortless</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>opinion on the fact of opinions may be facts that are opinions on facts?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 8:35 pm

Q: opinion on the fact of opinions may be facts that are opinions on facts?

A: thank you for that bit of wordplay</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i stop dreaming?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 9:04 pm

Q: how do i stop dreaming?

A: you might just have to make use of the dreams</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you own a hurdy gurdy?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 9:17 pm

Q: Do you own a hurdy gurdy?

A: never buy, always rent a hurdy gurdy</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How much did those special sandals cost?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 9:27 pm

Q: How much did those special sandals cost?

A: they were a reward for solving a riddle</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i feel like music is the only way for me to really feel anything anymore. i started learning debussy's first arabesque today and it didnt make me cry but it gave me a feeling of great sentimentality, if you know what i mean. or maybe thats just because im going through a particularly rough time right now</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 9:41 pm

Q: i feel like music is the only way for me to really feel anything anymore. i started learning debussy's first arabesque today and it didnt make me cry but it gave me a feeling of great sentimentality, if you know what i mean. or maybe thats just because im going through a particularly rough time right now

A: most importantly, it gives you something to do. something to focus on. in this case, something which promises (or at least intends to promise) to be lovely</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is steve's real name</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 10:00 pm

Q: What is steve's real name

A: the same as yours</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is history actually just a conspiracy perpetrated by the present to make itself seem more legitimate than it actually is?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.7.26 10:25 pm

Q: Is history actually just a conspiracy perpetrated by the present to make itself seem more legitimate than it actually is?

A: no</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Favourite number?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 12:18 am

Q: Favourite number?

A: if i could see a list of all of them that would help me decide</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What meaning do you find in creating things? I'm still struggling to find mine</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 12:31 am

Q: What meaning do you find in creating things? I'm still struggling to find mine

A: at some point you have to figure out what you'd honestly wish for</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is it party time?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 12:55 am

Q: Is it party time?

A: i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you most often enjoy your cinnamon rolls with or without the frosting?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 12:59 am

Q: do you most often enjoy your cinnamon rolls with or without the frosting?

A: i might say wait for something not so sweet to put frosting on. cinnamon roll is already sweet. a plain roll? definitely needs the frosting</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm trying to learn two languages at once. It's going ok so far, but do you think this is a bad idea in the long run?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 1:12 am

Q: I'm trying to learn two languages at once. It's going ok so far, but do you think this is a bad idea in the long run?

A: no i think it's good as long as you are enjoying it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Your toes are always touching, you just don't realise it</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 2:32 am

Q: Your toes are always touching, you just don't realise it

A: that's not true. 1: i can realize when they do, and 2: i am capable of stretching them so they dont touch</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>If steve doesn't have a job, why does he have to pay taxes? Also, the mail woman, since she's got a job, does she pay her taxes?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 2:39 am

Q: If steve doesn't have a job, why does he have to pay taxes? Also, the mail woman, since she's got a job, does she pay her taxes?

A: i left that part out</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is there no stranger strange enough?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 3:23 am

Q: is there no stranger strange enough?

A: thank you for referencing that lyric here</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I had hash browns at my local Denny's and they were delicious !!!</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 3:43 am

Q: I had hash browns at my local Denny's and they were delicious !!!

A: i want to believe you</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Now that i think about it, triangles are so fundamental they even became an instrument that is widely used. In contrast, I have never heard of a heptagon being used as an instrument.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 4:17 am

Q: Now that i think about it, triangles are so fundamental they even became an instrument that is widely used. In contrast, I have never heard of a heptagon being used as an instrument.

A: heptagons are, for sure, less fundamental</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what do you think about all the digits in the current year adding up to 10</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 4:54 am

Q: what do you think about all the digits in the current year adding up to 10

A: that will be happening every 9 years for a while</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When will Hell freeze over?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 6:18 am

Q: When will Hell freeze over?

A: some other time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>just to confirm: when you made the "i'm sad" song, were you sad?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 6:54 am

Q: just to confirm: when you made the "i'm sad" song, were you sad?

A: no. i was testing that out as a song hook, as well as some others. those tests actually made me very happy. they were empowering to me</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>1+1=?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 8:02 am

Q: 1+1=?

A: 11</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>are people built to be famous?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 8:25 am

Q: are people built to be famous?

A: was a dog built for stairs? ....Potentially. there's a lot of potential things we are equpped for even if it's not always the most common outcome</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if the world was to turn all languages into one to create a ''universal language'', what would it be called?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 8:57 am

Q: if the world was to turn all languages into one to create a ''universal language'', what would it be called?

A: the "universal language"</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why are some people so fucking rude</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 8:59 am

Q: why are some people so fucking rude

A: they are possibly still enraged about someone else being rude to them just moments before</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you been to earth</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 9:28 am

Q: have you been to earth

A: still there</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why can't I get myself to do the stuff I wanna do</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 9:42 am

Q: Why can't I get myself to do the stuff I wanna do

A: because you dont know exactly how</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do I overlay my neurocognitive processing bandwidth onto the object's quantum decoherence matrix?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 11:22 am

Q: How do I overlay my neurocognitive processing bandwidth onto the object's quantum decoherence matrix?

A: why not just use 'the force'</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>thoughts on the cold?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 12:03 pm

Q: thoughts on the cold?

A: it must be warm some other time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to detect sarcasm</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 12:19 pm

Q: how to detect sarcasm

A: this might work: watch some movies in foreign languages. this may give you some practice in detecting people's feelings through their communication, without being distracted by the 'correct' meanings of the individual words they are saying</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is there more to life?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 1:01 pm

Q: is there more to life?

A: yes there is. of course i dont know what you have found so far, but, regardless, there is more</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sometimes I feel like an alien. Obviously everyone's brain works differently, but sometimes your brain works so differently that it's hard to relate to others and get along with them the way the average person does. It's like the path my brain takes to make a joke or reference is so far away from what other people's brains would do that I just come off as strange. I don't think there's anything wrong with being strange, but it makes me sad sometimes. I can see the look on their face when they have the moment of realizing "oh, he's not like me". Have you ever struggled with feeling this way? Sometimes it feels like there is a language barrier even when we're both speaking the same language.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 2:36 pm

Q: Sometimes I feel like an alien. Obviously everyone's brain works differently, but sometimes your brain works so differently that it's hard to relate to others and get along with them the way the average person does. It's like the path my brain takes to make a joke or reference is so far away from what other people's brains would do that I just come off as strange. I don't think there's anything wrong with being strange, but it makes me sad sometimes. I can see the look on their face when they have the moment of realizing "oh, he's not like me". Have you ever struggled with feeling this way? Sometimes it feels like there is a language barrier even when we're both speaking the same language.

A: the reward for bridging this gap in communication is monumental. you will be able to show them things that they've never dreamed of</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>whats your favourite chord extension?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 2:38 pm

Q: whats your favourite chord extension?

A: the 'chord extension' is a myth. imagine if the letter 'd' anywhere it occurs was considered a 'word extension'. i'm pretty sure the only reason it's called an extension is because it happens to be in chapter 4 of your textbook and not 1, for some reason chapter 1 only has words without d in it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>favorite They Might Be Giants moment?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 2:45 pm

Q: favorite They Might Be Giants moment?

A: their name kind of scares me so i've honestly never listened to their music. i will eventually i promise</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I just finished one of the hardest semesters in my uni. Assignments up the roof, lab reports, presentations , exams and all, and i finally finished on Friday. In these 2 days of freedom, i went to a mountain for a hike, i went to the movies, played some basketball and socialized a lot and felt refreshed. But now the new semester starts from tomorrow, and while being easier than the last one, i feel so burnt out that i believe i ll need weeks to recover. But i cant just stop, i need to keep up cause this may be my final semester of uni. How can i push myself to go forward while still remaining sane? What do you do when you are burnt out?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 3:20 pm

Q: I just finished one of the hardest semesters in my uni. Assignments up the roof, lab reports, presentations , exams and all, and i finally finished on Friday. In these 2 days of freedom, i went to a mountain for a hike, i went to the movies, played some basketball and socialized a lot and felt refreshed. But now the new semester starts from tomorrow, and while being easier than the last one, i feel so burnt out that i believe i ll need weeks to recover. But i cant just stop, i need to keep up cause this may be my final semester of uni. How can i push myself to go forward while still remaining sane? What do you do when you are burnt out?

A: in your situation i would keep a journal probably</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Are we in reality?...</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 3:45 pm

Q: Are we in reality?...

A: what else would there be, and what would its qualities be</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How to play chords on recorder?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 3:54 pm

Q: How to play chords on recorder?

A: you may have to record it, no pun intended</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thoughts on this year's Super Bowl?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 4:08 pm

Q: Thoughts on this year's Super Bowl?

A: i haven't gotten around to thinking about it yet, but dont worry i will</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is it called a pick if it's still picking?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 5:24 pm

Q: Why is it called a pick if it's still picking?

A: why wouldnt it be</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>If I remember correctly, you often implied in your answers that the fear of not finishing a project can bring you closer to finishing it. I've been working on a personal editing project on and off for over 2 years now. Finishing it would be absolutely monumental and would change my life pretty significantly. And yet I can't seem to develop a fear of never finishing it. I don't think it's because I don't care too much about it, I really do. Maybe it's because the consequences of not finishing it would not be all too catastrophic from a financial perspective, so I don't really feel pressured in that way. What would you suggest I should do, in order to complete my project?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 5:33 pm

Q: If I remember correctly, you often implied in your answers that the fear of not finishing a project can bring you closer to finishing it. I've been working on a personal editing project on and off for over 2 years now. Finishing it would be absolutely monumental and would change my life pretty significantly. And yet I can't seem to develop a fear of never finishing it. I don't think it's because I don't care too much about it, I really do. Maybe it's because the consequences of not finishing it would not be all too catastrophic from a financial perspective, so I don't really feel pressured in that way. What would you suggest I should do, in order to complete my project?

A: in that case, i'm sorry to inform you........ everything seems to be going fine</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i had a strategy that worked for a while but now im gonna go ahead and answer to some impulses</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 6:13 pm

Q: i had a strategy that worked for a while but now im gonna go ahead and answer to some impulses

A: ah, the circle of life</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if i steal something from myself is it still a theft?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 6:27 pm

Q: if i steal something from myself is it still a theft?

A: it's a 'weird trick'</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is calculus difficult</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 6:59 pm

Q: Why is calculus difficult

A: something's gotta be difficult</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>im currently making a country. however most people who are into "Micronations" annoy me like hell. do you get it. do you get why micronations are both cool and annoying</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 7:42 pm

Q: im currently making a country. however most people who are into "Micronations" annoy me like hell. do you get it. do you get why micronations are both cool and annoying

A: there's barely a thing on earth that's not both cool and annoying</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what animal do you think looks the best wearin a tophat</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 7:45 pm

Q: what animal do you think looks the best wearin a tophat

A: rabbit</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do I stop mentally reacting to the imagined threat of the next bad thing that will happen to me?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 10:05 pm

Q: how do I stop mentally reacting to the imagined threat of the next bad thing that will happen to me?

A: if you can find something interesting to work on......</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you ever lucid dreamt?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 10:11 pm

Q: have you ever lucid dreamt?

A: perhaps i am now, although if you read this you'll know i'm not</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>when the heck will the fire music will come back</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 10:31 pm

Q: when the heck will the fire music will come back

A: i am cooking up much more</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why is the "q" in ueqstions green</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 10:35 pm

Q: why is the "q" in ueqstions green

A: because it's the first letter of the word</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>opinions on wd-40?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 11:23 pm

Q: opinions on wd-40?

A: it's famous</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you even "yes and-" an idea? i always cut ideas short by thinking they're no good.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.8.26 11:46 pm

Q: how do you even "yes and-" an idea? i always cut ideas short by thinking they're no good.

A: how about "yes and that idea sucks"</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How much wood could a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck... uh... I forgot the rest of the question. Can you tell me?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 1:13 am

Q: How much wood could a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck... uh... I forgot the rest of the question. Can you tell me?

A: "felt like it"</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how the h-e-double-hockey-sticks do i get this thing done before valentines????? i planned out very long work blocks for multiple days so that it would get done on the 14th, and i did follow through with all of that... but i underestimated the work and realized that the goal for each work block was not met EVEN WITH full focus and energy. now im super duper very behind schedule. the planned release date is crucial to this project, whar the ffffrick am i gonna do other than panic.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 1:46 am

Q: how the h-e-double-hockey-sticks do i get this thing done before valentines????? i planned out very long work blocks for multiple days so that it would get done on the 14th, and i did follow through with all of that... but i underestimated the work and realized that the goal for each work block was not met EVEN WITH full focus and energy. now im super duper very behind schedule. the planned release date is crucial to this project, whar the ffffrick am i gonna do other than panic.

A: how about this, lie down and very calmly panic for just 10 minutes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>where am i supposed to find freedom?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 3:19 am

Q: where am i supposed to find freedom?

A: start right there</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how did we decide how long time is?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 3:25 am

Q: how did we decide how long time is?

A: i'm not sure. i dont even think we know how long it is</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I am an idiot. Explain how do you answer your questions and make stuff better and be very honest about people (for some reason I want to be honest but I can't)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 8:27 am

Q: I am an idiot. Explain how do you answer your questions and make stuff better and be very honest about people (for some reason I want to be honest but I can't)

A: sometimes you have to introduce yourself to yourself</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>on a scale from funky to froovy to groovy, how's your day</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 8:46 am

Q: on a scale from funky to froovy to groovy, how's your day

A: pretty good</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>would it be too unfair of me to think of a character's lifestyle too often</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 10:19 am

Q: would it be too unfair of me to think of a character's lifestyle too often

A: i dont believe so</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if i pick up a mountain and hide in a suitcase, do i take the mountain with me?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 10:38 am

Q: if i pick up a mountain and hide in a suitcase, do i take the mountain with me?

A: not necessarily</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you listen to music?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 10:44 am

Q: do you listen to music?

A: from time to time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hey bill! what's your favorite olympic event?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 11:03 am

Q: hey bill! what's your favorite olympic event?

A: judging</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is a hotdog</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 11:16 am

Q: What is a hotdog

A: i have no earthly idea</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to ensure that the world is going to be either the same or better while i'm here and when i'm gone (not worse. the plan is to avoid this)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 11:50 am

Q: how to ensure that the world is going to be either the same or better while i'm here and when i'm gone (not worse. the plan is to avoid this)

A: you being born already accomplishes this</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hunger is to thirst what starvation is to what word?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 11:53 am

Q: Hunger is to thirst what starvation is to what word?

A: i only know it in 3 words, "dying of thirst". some things it takes 3 words to say, such as.... "three word phrase"</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hey bill, every time i feel uneasiness disturbs my personal flow i watch your videos and songs and read things here. Could you suggest another way of doing that?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 12:08 pm

Q: hey bill, every time i feel uneasiness disturbs my personal flow i watch your videos and songs and read things here. Could you suggest another way of doing that?

A: try watching them backwards</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>any recommendations for new flavors of peanut butter?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 12:34 pm

Q: any recommendations for new flavors of peanut butter?

A: oreo cookie</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How to accept failure?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 12:36 pm

Q: How to accept failure?

A: start working on the next thing</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you make songs with uncommon time signatures like i wanna be a movie star sounds so good?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 1:04 pm

Q: how do you make songs with uncommon time signatures like i wanna be a movie star sounds so good?

A: that's just how the idea came to me. you can't control what ideas come to you, and if you try, the idea gods are like "hm, no ideas for you". then when you least expect it "pow, idea" and if that idea has 9 beats then that's just how it goes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why do the two people in "Perfect." randomly get in sync when talking</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 2:31 pm

Q: why do the two people in "Perfect." randomly get in sync when talking

A: you know how sometimes suddenly the truth is so obvious, everyone in the room says it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>can you give a bad answer to this question</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 2:52 pm

Q: can you give a bad answer to this question

A: the circumstance of this question makes this a paradoxical task i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes i was going to say yes but now that i think about it no</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you even SURVIVE someone asking about genres</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 3:58 pm

Q: how do you even SURVIVE someone asking about genres

A: sometimes i lash out</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ok but what if i DO call it "ueqstions" in plaintext, for the sake of the proverbial joy and whimsy</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 4:17 pm

Q: ok but what if i DO call it "ueqstions" in plaintext, for the sake of the proverbial joy and whimsy

A: to me it will always look like someone misunderstanding the title design, but my view is not necessarily so important</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you consider yourself a philosopher?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 4:26 pm

Q: do you consider yourself a philosopher?

A: only if absolutely necessary</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>has this been asked before</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 5:19 pm

Q: has this been asked before

A: yes it has</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>where can i find willpower and grow as a person? it feels unfair to me that so many people get it from birth meanwhile i feel empty</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 5:39 pm

Q: where can i find willpower and grow as a person? it feels unfair to me that so many people get it from birth meanwhile i feel empty

A: you've already discovered that you want to, now it's just as soon as some of the envy settles down a bit and you'll be on your way with your own unique brand of personal growth</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>should I call this page the questions page or the ueqstions page (asking for a friend)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 7:06 pm

Q: should I call this page the questions page or the ueqstions page (asking for a friend)

A: questions</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is mt st helens still feeling crazy and adventurous or has it settled into a more formal and casual lifestyle?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 7:24 pm

Q: is mt st helens still feeling crazy and adventurous or has it settled into a more formal and casual lifestyle?

A: we're in fictional territory with this but let's just say you can expect a telephone call soon from Mt St Helens itself and then you'll know all the answers and more</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you play any games?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 8:23 pm

Q: Do you play any games?

A: yes but i dont always win</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>as of writing this it's been a month and two days since you answered my first question. you answered it on my birthday, which made me happy. the question was: what is the current salmon count? you replied with "oh maybe a handful" considering the time it's been, do you think the salmon count is more than a handful by now? like, the size of a loaf of bread, for example?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 8:59 pm

Q: as of writing this it's been a month and two days since you answered my first question. you answered it on my birthday, which made me happy. the question was: what is the current salmon count? you replied with "oh maybe a handful" considering the time it's been, do you think the salmon count is more than a handful by now? like, the size of a loaf of bread, for example?

A: this is a reference to a musical transition in a song video. there were some fast chords flying by just before the next verse, and to depict this on screen i stacked up a bunch of salmon fish. with a caption on screen that said "salmon count", counting them up. i dont recall what the total was, but the video has not changed since it was released. i've never heard this phrase in any other context</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i play a chord on the triangle</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 9:19 pm

Q: how do i play a chord on the triangle

A: i was going to say you need two triangles but even then it's dicey because those things kind of dont really ring on an exact pitch. but if you get two different sizes and strike them at the same time i believe you can claim it's a chord. especially if you get 3 different sizes but you may need some assistence from other musicians to execute this, or else record yourself 3 times</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>you ever just ;;;;;;;;;;;;;;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 10:12 pm

Q: you ever just ;;;;;;;;;;;;;;

A: yes i do</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>thoughts?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 10:17 pm

Q: thoughts?

A: yes thoughts. that is correct</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>sorry for this question... but how can i have hope that things might work out for me in the future when i can't imagine myself being the kind of person i wish to be, nor can i imagine how to possibly getting to a point where i feel more secure/happy? everything is so hard for me. am i just fucked?? i know you say that people get tired of normal, but i'd give anything to make myself normally functional, just to see what that might feel like. my brain is broken or something</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 10:46 pm

Q: sorry for this question... but how can i have hope that things might work out for me in the future when i can't imagine myself being the kind of person i wish to be, nor can i imagine how to possibly getting to a point where i feel more secure/happy? everything is so hard for me. am i just fucked?? i know you say that people get tired of normal, but i'd give anything to make myself normally functional, just to see what that might feel like. my brain is broken or something

A: write 9 other versions of this, based on how you are feeling over the next 9 days</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>whats your favorite letter of the alphabet?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.9.26 11:49 pm

Q: whats your favorite letter of the alphabet?

A: i have to combine different letters together. that's the only thing that does it for me anymore</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is music actually good</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 12:11 am

Q: is music actually good

A: it's impossible for it to be actually good, which is why it seems so miraculous when it somehow is</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do I go the right road in life when I DONT HAVE A CAR!?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 2:02 am

Q: how do I go the right road in life when I DONT HAVE A CAR!?

A: according to the metaphor you are using ('road in life'), anything is a car</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>are you ever in a bad mental spot but then you realize you can just stop the bad thoughts and get a little jiggy with it?, (for example dancing)?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 5:04 am

Q: are you ever in a bad mental spot but then you realize you can just stop the bad thoughts and get a little jiggy with it?, (for example dancing)?

A: can happen. not necessarily always invoking the will smith reference per se, mais oui, on peut 'rock out' de temps en temps, sorry just learning english</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you have a "thinking voice"? people describe it as an actual voice in their head that "narrates their thoughts", but i don't think i have it. although at some point in the past, i feel like i did</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 7:34 am

Q: do you have a "thinking voice"? people describe it as an actual voice in their head that "narrates their thoughts", but i don't think i have it. although at some point in the past, i feel like i did

A: sometimes it may be useful to create this by speaking on recording. it can help to sort out your thoughts. sometimes something comes out that was missed before when you were thinking voicelessly</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Would you call a chord that consists of B, E, and G# in that order an E/B?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 8:00 am

Q: Would you call a chord that consists of B, E, and G# in that order an E/B?

A: usually the slash notation ("E over B") means the B is actually a bass note. what i'm trying to say is, if you played only those 3 notes in a chord in the mid range (like around middle C) i dont think you'd wanna call it E/B because the B wont feel like a bass note because it's just not low enough. (and if all 3 notes were played in the bass range that would of course not sound like a chord either, it would be sludge). how about this: play B, E, and G# around the middle C range, then one octave below the B, play an additional B in the bass. now you have the sound of something that would rightfully be written on the page as "E/B", pronounced "E over B", or "E with B in the bass"</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ever since watching your 3D skit-type videos like Perfect and 2 Friends on the Beach, it's changed my perception of your play featuring the iPhone power block and the mechanical pencil from all the way back in 2014. I now see that video as a sort of prototype or precursor of those later skit-type videos; I could easily see those two friends on the beach having a very similar conversation to the one the power brick and mechanical pencil had all those years ago, and that's given me additional respect for that original video from 2014 than I maybe had before. Do you think of that video in a similar way?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 10:11 am

Q: Ever since watching your 3D skit-type videos like Perfect and 2 Friends on the Beach, it's changed my perception of your play featuring the iPhone power block and the mechanical pencil from all the way back in 2014. I now see that video as a sort of prototype or precursor of those later skit-type videos; I could easily see those two friends on the beach having a very similar conversation to the one the power brick and mechanical pencil had all those years ago, and that's given me additional respect for that original video from 2014 than I maybe had before. Do you think of that video in a similar way?

A: of course</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is writing songs fun for you?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 10:39 am

Q: is writing songs fun for you?

A: more than fun</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Would Anglo Saxon be a good name for a goldfish, what if I had 2 goldfish, what if I named them Anglo and Sacon respectively?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 10:39 am

Q: Would Anglo Saxon be a good name for a goldfish, what if I had 2 goldfish, what if I named them Anglo and Sacon respectively?

A: they might try to name you something</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why does my voice sound worse the more i care about the outcome of the recording?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 11:08 am

Q: why does my voice sound worse the more i care about the outcome of the recording?

A: because it's distracting you from how it really feels to sing the thing you're singing</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When you talk do people listen?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 11:40 am

Q: When you talk do people listen?

A: sometimes they do</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do some of your songs have more abstract meanings than others</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 11:40 am

Q: do some of your songs have more abstract meanings than others

A: maybe, although there's not really any way to measure this</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thoughts on February?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 1:23 pm

Q: Thoughts on February?

A: short and sweet</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Was the questions page always like this or did it get improved over time?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 2:25 pm

Q: Was the questions page always like this or did it get improved over time?

A: there have been very tiny improvements that would mostly go unnoticed</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I noticed that some of your older music seems to have instrumentation that seems mostly consistent across the song, whereas your newer music has instrumentation that rapidly changes. Do you think making short jingles for a while affected this?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 3:25 pm

Q: I noticed that some of your older music seems to have instrumentation that seems mostly consistent across the song, whereas your newer music has instrumentation that rapidly changes. Do you think making short jingles for a while affected this?

A: no i dont believe so, i think it was a new technique i discovered around 2015 that i specifically needed for longer songs</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>as you have seen several years of questions come through this box, what are the truly evergreen events, the things that actually get asked about every single year at the same time? i.e. the olympics, the super bowl, that sort of thing</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 3:40 pm

Q: as you have seen several years of questions come through this box, what are the truly evergreen events, the things that actually get asked about every single year at the same time? i.e. the olympics, the super bowl, that sort of thing

A: (olympics are not every year, right?) "new years resolutions", "valentines day", many many other calendar events throughout the year, surely most of them youve heard of, people talk about the school schedule, graduation, going back to school or going to a new school in august/september, people begin talking about halloween in august, christmas/holidays are always talked about, all four named calendar seasons are talked about, plenty of other special days with puns and song references, multiple september song references are made in september (EWF, greenday, me), and much more</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you ever run a blackjack business</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 4:03 pm

Q: have you ever run a blackjack business

A: no i dont believe so</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When was the last time you drank water?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 4:27 pm

Q: When was the last time you drank water?

A: moments ago</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what was the first instrument you learned</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 4:51 pm

Q: what was the first instrument you learned

A: piano or drums</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you have any taco preferences?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 5:16 pm

Q: Do you have any taco preferences?

A: i prefer to be surprised by what taco it is</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What's your opinion on "9 8 7"?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 5:44 pm

Q: What's your opinion on "9 8 7"?

A: it would be hard to stop me from doing a song about numbers</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What music genre are you?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 6:09 pm

Q: What music genre are you?

A: "whatever gets the job done"</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what are your thoughts on comic sans</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 6:16 pm

Q: what are your thoughts on comic sans

A: commands respect</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the end of the world a good thing?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 7:18 pm

Q: Is the end of the world a good thing?

A: sometimes one world ending gives way for another to begin</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why did the road cross the chicken</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 8:02 pm

Q: why did the road cross the chicken

A: sort of a pre-emptive strike</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why does having a fake nemesis motivate me so much?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 9:10 pm

Q: Why does having a fake nemesis motivate me so much?

A: you may be naturally competitive</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>are you left- or right-handed?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 10:10 pm

Q: are you left- or right-handed?

A: i'll say this much, i ride goofy footed</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why does chess make me really angry</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 10:35 pm

Q: why does chess make me really angry

A: maybe it's just because your opponent is trying to destroy you in the game and make you lose</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>opinions on vhs?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 10:44 pm

Q: opinions on vhs?

A: "be kind, please rewind" or "be a jerk and leave the tape at the end"</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you played a game before</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 11:00 pm

Q: have you played a game before

A: that's preposterous. who do you think i am</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is the first word in one of the projects you're working on?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.10.26 11:18 pm

Q: what is the first word in one of the projects you're working on?

A: it wouldnt make sense out of context</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Answering with one word. describe the lighting of the room you are in.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 12:00 am

Q: Answering with one word. describe the lighting of the room you are in.

A: sensible</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What should i draw today</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 12:36 am

Q: What should i draw today

A: how about part of a handkercheif</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how did the guys hat get bent in "slow down" ?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 12:51 am

Q: how did the guys hat get bent in "slow down" ?

A: i bent it. a songwriting trick, sometimes, is to go ahead and bend a hat</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>are you good at connect 4?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 1:42 am

Q: are you good at connect 4?

A: my high score in connect 4 is 3</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>just said the word 'peak' today and I think it's the first time I've used it unironically</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 3:55 am

Q: just said the word 'peak' today and I think it's the first time I've used it unironically

A: it's all down hill from here</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Idk why but the voice in my head narrating all my thoughts can switch from my voice to another voice i've heard a solid amount of. Is that something your internal monologue can do? Or am I just weird?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 6:35 am

Q: Idk why but the voice in my head narrating all my thoughts can switch from my voice to another voice i've heard a solid amount of. Is that something your internal monologue can do? Or am I just weird?

A: it's normal if you've been listening to someone a lot lately, you start to imagine things in their voice</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what do you think of poetry</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 8:00 am

Q: what do you think of poetry

A: so crazy it just might work</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the universe a cycle?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 8:02 am

Q: Is the universe a cycle?

A: there are many cycles in it, then there are also things that progress uniquely forward</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Should I drop out of school and peruse my dreams of working a ferry boat? The lake calls for me every time I stare out my window</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 9:21 am

Q: Should I drop out of school and peruse my dreams of working a ferry boat? The lake calls for me every time I stare out my window

A: maybe after it calls 2 or 3 more times</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you think every single decision we make is intertwined together, and just by making one small change, we change the trajectory of the entire universe? does that make us god, or atleast extremely powerful?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 11:00 am

Q: do you think every single decision we make is intertwined together, and just by making one small change, we change the trajectory of the entire universe? does that make us god, or atleast extremely powerful?

A: if we all are that powerful then do you suppose the powers would kind of all balance out</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ideal pb to j ratio?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 11:05 am

Q: ideal pb to j ratio?

A: they have the ideal sandwich on display for reference at the International Bureau of Weights and Measures</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>can you make a water-flavored bread</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 11:06 am

Q: can you make a water-flavored bread

A: wonderbread is water flavored</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i overcome creative block when writing music?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 11:44 am

Q: how do i overcome creative block when writing music?

A: sooner or later you will find your own enjoyment. if you are too stubborn and continually refuse, it will find you anyway</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why does the things i wanna do seem so difficult to start?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 12:35 pm

Q: Why does the things i wanna do seem so difficult to start?

A: to make it more rewarding to accomplish</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you make your music? it sounds really good :3</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 1:11 pm

Q: how do you make your music? it sounds really good :3

A: my secret trick is to try to make it sound really bad</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do printers work?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 1:58 pm

Q: How do printers work?

A: i'm not totally sure</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you ever feel like you have no controll over your life? like you're expected to do these things? How do you handle that?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 2:17 pm

Q: do you ever feel like you have no controll over your life? like you're expected to do these things? How do you handle that?

A: sometimes you can find different ways to do those things, within the requirements</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why do chords on piano on the lowest octave (and partially on the one above) sound so unintelligible?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 3:12 pm

Q: Why do chords on piano on the lowest octave (and partially on the one above) sound so unintelligible?

A: what i know even less is why can we see only one octave of color</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do you focus on solving the problem over trying to escape it</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 3:43 pm

Q: How do you focus on solving the problem over trying to escape it

A: identifying the problem is sometimes important</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is your favorite container</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 4:43 pm

Q: what is your favorite container

A: the box.... from when people say "think outside the box"</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you think that world has gotten more immature</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 5:28 pm

Q: Do you think that world has gotten more immature

A: i collect clips and excerpts of people saying that at all different times in history, for good luck</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Am I a banjo?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 5:30 pm

Q: Am I a banjo?

A: no i dont believe so</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can isn't a very common name, why is that?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 5:35 pm

Q: Can isn't a very common name, why is that?

A: most people are just busy having other names</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what's your third least favorite food</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 5:36 pm

Q: what's your third least favorite food

A: there are at least 10 that i may have blocked out of my memory entirely</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What's something you're sure about?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 6:42 pm

Q: What's something you're sure about?

A: i'm sure that there are things i'm unsure about</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>can you tell me a secret about me?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 6:52 pm

Q: can you tell me a secret about me?

A: not if you've done a good enough job keeping it secret</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>can you estimate how many feet are in a kilometer without looking it up</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 8:14 pm

Q: can you estimate how many feet are in a kilometer without looking it up

A: based on some of the speed limit signs i've seen, maybe it's about 3000</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is it mean if multiple people consider me their best friend when i myself dont have a best friend?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 9:25 pm

Q: is it mean if multiple people consider me their best friend when i myself dont have a best friend?

A: it's an interesting thought experiment</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what's your favorite thing to do on neptune?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 10:22 pm

Q: what's your favorite thing to do on neptune?

A: try to find a way out of neptune</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Still waiting on for new Damien Maymdiem lore</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 10:52 pm

Q: Still waiting on for new Damien Maymdiem lore

A: working on some new and different lore for you to wait on more lore for</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Based on your previous advice I rented five hurdy gurdies and now I'm stuck in the middle of nowhere somewhere and everywhere all at once what do I do now?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 11:24 pm

Q: Based on your previous advice I rented five hurdy gurdies and now I'm stuck in the middle of nowhere somewhere and everywhere all at once what do I do now?

A: begin a multi-generational comic strip franchise</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How close are you to understanding the secret workings of the Universe?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 11:26 pm

Q: How close are you to understanding the secret workings of the Universe?

A: they are again and again very relatable and familiar, but there's an unlimited amount, and also an unlimited amout of ways to understand, while still remains an unlimited amount of mystery</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>best time zone?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.11.26 11:43 pm

Q: best time zone?

A: 0</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>yoo. Whats gud dwg . you ever wonder like about the status quo or whatever? cuz if there's uh like for example, a problem with how negatively people react to something you want to say, then youd well maybe youd want to show everyone the right way and fight against said pre-concieved notions. but also when interacting with someone and ur thinking about emotional impact and all that stuff then you have to take into account that they'll react negatively without knowing there's a problem with that, and you may want to avoid saying the thing that makes people react that way. of course, there's stuff to be said about whether there actually is a problem with their reaction, but that's a different convo Did i explain all this right? basically i want 2 argue about the system but ppl have an attachment to it that i respect</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 12:47 am

Q: yoo. Whats gud dwg . you ever wonder like about the status quo or whatever? cuz if there's uh like for example, a problem with how negatively people react to something you want to say, then youd well maybe youd want to show everyone the right way and fight against said pre-concieved notions. but also when interacting with someone and ur thinking about emotional impact and all that stuff then you have to take into account that they'll react negatively without knowing there's a problem with that, and you may want to avoid saying the thing that makes people react that way. of course, there's stuff to be said about whether there actually is a problem with their reaction, but that's a different convo Did i explain all this right? basically i want 2 argue about the system but ppl have an attachment to it that i respect

A: there are all kinds of ways for different things to be said, reacted to, and more. you've told a story about a bit of conflict in this area but i believe that's just the tip of the ice berg</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can I become a banjo by avoiding what the not banjos do?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 12:55 am

Q: Can I become a banjo by avoiding what the not banjos do?

A: not exactly</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Reading these is comforting. This is the last text on the internet that I can feel reasonably confident isn't Ai generated or targeted to sell me something based on the entire history of my digital existence. It's authentic here. I read these when the world makes me sad. Thanks</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 1:10 am

Q: Reading these is comforting. This is the last text on the internet that I can feel reasonably confident isn't Ai generated or targeted to sell me something based on the entire history of my digital existence. It's authentic here. I read these when the world makes me sad. Thanks

A: makes you realize the great value of building trust</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what if i can't sing</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 4:46 am

Q: what if i can't sing

A: you can do something else, but also sometimes people who say they can't sing can sing</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>opinions on fanfic</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 5:35 am

Q: opinions on fanfic

A: simultaneously overrated and underrated</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you think all artists struggle to communicate in any other way (other then art)?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 5:36 am

Q: do you think all artists struggle to communicate in any other way (other then art)?

A: surely not all, but, some</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how are you the greatest being to ever exist</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 8:45 am

Q: how are you the greatest being to ever exist

A: perhaps you've simply drunk the kool aid</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you want to know what I think about business meetings?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 9:37 am

Q: Do you want to know what I think about business meetings?

A: sure</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why is "out for lunch" so much more popular than "out for dinner" or "out for breakfast"?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 9:48 am

Q: why is "out for lunch" so much more popular than "out for dinner" or "out for breakfast"?

A: in general it may be more common for people to do their professional work in the middle of the day. so if they go out for a meal in the middle of the work day it will most often be lunch time</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is there a difference between choosing to not choose and not choosing to choose?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 10:18 am

Q: is there a difference between choosing to not choose and not choosing to choose?

A: yes i believe so</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How many roads must a man walk down?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 11:29 am

Q: How many roads must a man walk down?

A: any number will be fine</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what's the most random thing in the universe?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 1:23 pm

Q: what's the most random thing in the universe?

A: if anything is 'most random', it would be by definition not random. random needs a whole equal field of choices</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Your song "The road" seems to be heavy with meaning. There is something portentous about it. Was there something at the time that had an influence on your writing? Is there a deeper context? Or am I just loosing it about some lyrics that sounded nice to you? Love this song, love your work!</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 1:55 pm

Q: Your song "The road" seems to be heavy with meaning. There is something portentous about it. Was there something at the time that had an influence on your writing? Is there a deeper context? Or am I just loosing it about some lyrics that sounded nice to you? Love this song, love your work!

A: they tend to come out this way when i write them from beginning to end on paper all at once. also, where you mention 'lyrics', i think 'music' is at least as much to blame for any of the deep places this one might go</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is it safe to assume the world won't end later today?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 3:03 pm

Q: is it safe to assume the world won't end later today?

A: yes i believe so</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>an annoying issue i discovered is i get really excited about what im about to learn in college, so i research it on my own, but this leads to me being really bored when said subject begins in class so i stop paying attention and then suddenly the lecture gets to a level i didnt reach by myself and because i havent been paying attention im lost</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 4:08 pm

Q: an annoying issue i discovered is i get really excited about what im about to learn in college, so i research it on my own, but this leads to me being really bored when said subject begins in class so i stop paying attention and then suddenly the lecture gets to a level i didnt reach by myself and because i havent been paying attention im lost

A: maybe you could research it by yourself while sitting in class</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to trust the right people and push through failure</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 4:28 pm

Q: how to trust the right people and push through failure

A: as if by magic</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is your philosophy?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 5:26 pm

Q: What is your philosophy?

A: you'd probably be able to see it better in the answer to almost any question other than this one</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I want to rule the world and cast a fireball and everyone dies except for the people I like who stay alive but the people I don't like they are going to die of course you are not going to die. Is that bad</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 5:59 pm

Q: I want to rule the world and cast a fireball and everyone dies except for the people I like who stay alive but the people I don't like they are going to die of course you are not going to die. Is that bad

A: it certainly sounds bad on paper</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>so you hate both pancakes and waffles?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 6:15 pm

Q: so you hate both pancakes and waffles?

A: no</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what color of light do you prefer</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 7:57 pm

Q: what color of light do you prefer

A: regular</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to commit to something even if i'm scared to do it? (college)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 9:18 pm

Q: how to commit to something even if i'm scared to do it? (college)

A: there's no way to explain it until after you've done it. and even then you still might not be able to explain how you did it. Unless youre not going to do it, in which case you may never know either</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>If I hear one pitch, I can usually tell what note it is, but if I'm listening to a song, I cannot tell what an individual note is anymore, you know what I mean?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 10:17 pm

Q: If I hear one pitch, I can usually tell what note it is, but if I'm listening to a song, I cannot tell what an individual note is anymore, you know what I mean?

A: most musicians are the opposite. they can tell notes musically but not without the music</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you think there is a universe where bikes don't exist?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 10:18 pm

Q: Do you think there is a universe where bikes don't exist?

A: sure</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is the 28th word in your next song</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 10:59 pm

Q: what is the 28th word in your next song

A: i'd rather just let you hear the whole song</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>will this question be answered?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 11:00 pm

Q: will this question be answered?

A: i'll see what i can do</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>should i start a video store?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.12.26 11:57 pm

Q: should i start a video store?

A: start 2 of them if you can</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why does the uestionsQ page use a Yellow-Purple-White colour scheme?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 12:39 am

Q: Why does the uestionsQ page use a Yellow-Purple-White colour scheme?

A: because i can</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you consider yourself as someone good in comedy</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 12:41 am

Q: do you consider yourself as someone good in comedy

A: you wont really catch me going "hey folks, heres some comedy [some stuff that was promised to be comedy], that was comedy" because i think doing that sucks, and that type of behaviour is especially bad for comedy of all things</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>were you excited when you first learned about math?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 12:43 am

Q: were you excited when you first learned about math?

A: yes i believe so, if i could even remember that far back</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Whats the meaning of life?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 1:33 am

Q: Whats the meaning of life?

A: there are unlimited meanings and unlimited meaning, in life. if you're having trouble finding it, then i wish you a meaningful search</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you think that part of what makes great artists so great is that they tend to think their art isn't so great? Some sort of humility-quality correlation? I know every artist is their own worst critic, but I also wonder if taking less pride in your work tends to boost a drive to improve.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 3:59 am

Q: Do you think that part of what makes great artists so great is that they tend to think their art isn't so great? Some sort of humility-quality correlation? I know every artist is their own worst critic, but I also wonder if taking less pride in your work tends to boost a drive to improve.

A: there's a lot of different ways for it to work. i think for many artists there can be deep feelings of doubt and dread, but sometimes it all comes down to those moments of sudden extreme self confidence, thinking for a moment that you can do anything. probably a lot of highs and lows may be common in artists. HOWEVER it could also be equally common for artists to have neither highs nor lows</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Have you written music an any mode other than ionian or aeolian</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 8:00 am

Q: Have you written music an any mode other than ionian or aeolian

A: sure. for those attempting to keep score on this (it may unravel a bit sometimes because things can move around) i think you'll find sufficient amounts of your friends 'dorian' and 'mixolydian', indesputably. for example, the verse vamps of "i'm scared" are decisively conveying 'mixolydian', and the verse vamps of '987' are definitely conveying 'dorian' but here's where the keeping score falls apart, for example: if you wanted to, you might be able to claim, for example, that the first 16 bars of 'princess' are 'lydian', because it starts on a G chord and all the melody can be clocked there as G lydian, but i just dont think it's right to call it Lydian, it's just D major starting from the 4 chord. heck you could even call that whole thing A mixolydian if you want. but to me that's just the key of D, and i think most songwriters would probably agree with me. what i'm trying to say is this happens to anyone, if you try to 'write something in lydian', F lydian for example, youre just going to find yourself in C after you write a couple of bars and get invested in what's happening. For example, it's like if you wanted to write a movie that takes place at the store..... well as soon as you write a couple of scenes and get invested in the characters, they're gonna eventually go home and you'll find out that they have a home, the store was not their home, even though it was in the first scene. anyway, the interlude vamp of 'ground plane' could be considered phrygian natural3, or mixolydian flat2 flat6 equivalently, whichever one gets you more experience points</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What **IS** ambition??</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 9:11 am

Q: What **IS** ambition??

A: wanting to do or accomplish something big</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you have any favorite music artists that inspired you to create your own music?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 9:26 am

Q: Do you have any favorite music artists that inspired you to create your own music?

A: even if i knew who my favorites were i still wouldnt know</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>something i've found is that whenever a teacher goes quiet, everyone starts paying attention, especially if they weren't doing so before. often for many reasons, such as the possibility of teachers going silent and staring at people to get them to pay attention. since everyone in the room realizes the teacher is silent, they look up to see if they're being stared at, even if they aren't. i believe that this technique is something that teachers should use more, and they should stop talking for the rest of the period.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 10:39 am

Q: something i've found is that whenever a teacher goes quiet, everyone starts paying attention, especially if they weren't doing so before. often for many reasons, such as the possibility of teachers going silent and staring at people to get them to pay attention. since everyone in the room realizes the teacher is silent, they look up to see if they're being stared at, even if they aren't. i believe that this technique is something that teachers should use more, and they should stop talking for the rest of the period.

A: the same exact thing is important in music, in movies, .... in music for movies, .... it's a super handy tool for any artist, "whatever youre doing, make sure you stop sometimes", that's kind of the only way to even get the best out of whatever that thing is</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thoughts on chairs</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 12:04 pm

Q: Thoughts on chairs

A: hard to believe</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how many picoseconds until more content</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 12:09 pm

Q: how many picoseconds until more content

A: at least a handful</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i become consistent in habits that i am trying to establish for the first time?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 12:26 pm

Q: how do i become consistent in habits that i am trying to establish for the first time?

A: the first time you cant be consistent yet. for the first time all you have to do is do it once. which goes a long way, because starting is a vitally important step</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what about life?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 1:57 pm

Q: what about life?

A: a lot of things are about life</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how important is the look of your instruments to you? I for one would really struggle to buy a instrument (let's say a guitar, coz pianos are generally not as diverse) I don't like visually, even if it had features I desired and/or was within my intended price range</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 2:36 pm

Q: how important is the look of your instruments to you? I for one would really struggle to buy a instrument (let's say a guitar, coz pianos are generally not as diverse) I don't like visually, even if it had features I desired and/or was within my intended price range

A: yes, having good looking things around is certainly good luck, and that's not a coincidence: because you see the things and it makes you feel good to see them and also makes you feel good about yourself</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to listen to new music? i want to hear a lot of all different kinds of songs but idk how to even begin doing that</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 4:22 pm

Q: how to listen to new music? i want to hear a lot of all different kinds of songs but idk how to even begin doing that

A: the dirty secret about music discovery is it often works best when the song comes to you, attached to a something palatable such as a movie or retail shopping experience</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do i become a pretty princess</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 4:42 pm

Q: How do i become a pretty princess

A: check to see if you arent already one, or else risk being double princess</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you ever feel like you're not you? If so, how do you stop making you feel like not being you? If not, do you like bugs?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 5:16 pm

Q: Do you ever feel like you're not you? If so, how do you stop making you feel like not being you? If not, do you like bugs?

A: it's like the weather. sometimes i feel i seem more like myself than other times</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>last month you wished a gizmo called "push buttons" existed. great news: the buttons on arcade machines are called push buttons! anyways how do you feel about pilk (pepsi and milk)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 6:02 pm

Q: last month you wished a gizmo called "push buttons" existed. great news: the buttons on arcade machines are called push buttons! anyways how do you feel about pilk (pepsi and milk)

A: i feel you should have several good creative outlets if you dont already have them</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you see it as a limitation (and I'm not saying that limitations are necessarily a bad thing) that since all the characters in your skit-type videos (Perfect, 2 Friends on a Beach) are voiced by you, they all sound like you? Would you ever get someone else to voice a character for that kind of video, if you wanted a character to sound drastically different? Or would you just use some kind of voice editing software?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 6:06 pm

Q: Do you see it as a limitation (and I'm not saying that limitations are necessarily a bad thing) that since all the characters in your skit-type videos (Perfect, 2 Friends on a Beach) are voiced by you, they all sound like you? Would you ever get someone else to voice a character for that kind of video, if you wanted a character to sound drastically different? Or would you just use some kind of voice editing software?

A: ultimately i consider it a positive limitation</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how much sand is there..... total???</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 6:20 pm

Q: how much sand is there..... total???

A: forgive me, i didn't count the sand</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what time of the universe is it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 6:47 pm

Q: what time of the universe is it?

A: this one, i dont know how else to describe it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why were most of your old songs in the key of e?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 7:31 pm

Q: Why were most of your old songs in the key of e?

A: you just happened to hear maybe 2 or 3 of them in a row and made a generalization which is not quite right</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what's your middle favourite question to be asked</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 7:55 pm

Q: what's your middle favourite question to be asked

A: this one</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When I need to save a project in my daw I usually close my eyes with the loop I made playing and try to think of a combination of words informed by the music. I end up with a bunch of file names like "nevadakedavra", "arctic crocs", "lemonshoom", basically a bunch of useless names I can't remember, but they're fun. Do you have a unique naming convention for your files? How do you organize your unfinished stuff before you've decided on names and things?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 8:35 pm

Q: When I need to save a project in my daw I usually close my eyes with the loop I made playing and try to think of a combination of words informed by the music. I end up with a bunch of file names like "nevadakedavra", "arctic crocs", "lemonshoom", basically a bunch of useless names I can't remember, but they're fun. Do you have a unique naming convention for your files? How do you organize your unfinished stuff before you've decided on names and things?

A: in general my songwriting usually includes words, so if there's words in it then it's usually easy to name, BUT, sometimes the very nascent song ideas and bits dont have any words yet, and by default they are often just named with the date/time but sometimes it is useful to name them abstractly as needed</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is it ever appropriate to be mean? Straight up nasty?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 10:27 pm

Q: Is it ever appropriate to be mean? Straight up nasty?

A: there's surely some context missing</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you ever look back on your life and wish you could have done more and feel regretful? if yes, what's your best advice on brushing past this and trying ignore the past and build yourself a better future?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.13.26 10:45 pm

Q: do you ever look back on your life and wish you could have done more and feel regretful? if yes, what's your best advice on brushing past this and trying ignore the past and build yourself a better future?

A: as soon as you get moving it will get better</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how did you hold on to this dream for so long? you must be pretty darn intelligent. when things get heavy, my brain puts the dream on pause, changes the channel, and loses the remote.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 12:39 am

Q: how did you hold on to this dream for so long? you must be pretty darn intelligent. when things get heavy, my brain puts the dream on pause, changes the channel, and loses the remote.

A: what do you switch to</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Were the '90s really the last "golden age" for American cinema?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 1:50 am

Q: Were the '90s really the last "golden age" for American cinema?

A: hahahaha no everyone always thinks the 'golden age' was some time in the past while never seeming to recognize anything golden about their current time period. time passing just brings fondness to memories, it seems. i have clips and references from yesteryear to prove this as a continuous phenomenon regardless of what date</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you ever overthought to the point where you just end up shutting down for a while because of how bad you made the situation in your head</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 1:54 am

Q: have you ever overthought to the point where you just end up shutting down for a while because of how bad you made the situation in your head

A: oh sure</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do i like men, women or (checks list) posters of stock photo sewage pipes?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 1:59 am

Q: do i like men, women or (checks list) posters of stock photo sewage pipes?

A: no need to decide right now. sometimes we have no way of even describing or predicting what we'll like</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>favorite baseball team?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 2:29 am

Q: favorite baseball team?

A: the westbound outsiders</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is so envelope-y about envelope filters?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 3:07 am

Q: what is so envelope-y about envelope filters?

A: heck, whats so envelopey about envelopes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you think you could remember all the songs you made</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 3:07 am

Q: do you think you could remember all the songs you made

A: i'm more focused on the ones i havent made yet</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is there such thing a stupid question?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 3:28 am

Q: is there such thing a stupid question?

A: yes but there's also stupid answers as well</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I think after reading some of your answers on questions i completely forgot, i've concluded that i Need to begin transcribing music to practice music like id practice listening and writing for a language. and i've began! am i on a good path? and what would you recommend i keep in mind (in general)((optional))? thank youu</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 4:04 am

Q: I think after reading some of your answers on questions i completely forgot, i've concluded that i Need to begin transcribing music to practice music like id practice listening and writing for a language. and i've began! am i on a good path? and what would you recommend i keep in mind (in general)((optional))? thank youu

A: this goes differently for everyone. i certainly had a pretty great time doing a lot of this when i was younger. it seems like it's working for you. it's a pretty easy game, you just keep doing it and you automatically get better and smarter and finding out more about yourself and the world</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i have a weird ego complex where i think i am the """"chosen one""" and this translates to a deep desire to do something very big and important with my life. now you may say "that's not a bad thing" well it makes my current life feel empty by comparison. now one could say 'oh change your life'. but i am 1) generally resistent to change and 2) actually quite content with my current life, at least most of the time. my overall view on this is that i think this desire is an unhealthy one, but i'm incapable of just, like, squashing it. do you have any advice</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 5:55 am

Q: i have a weird ego complex where i think i am the """"chosen one""" and this translates to a deep desire to do something very big and important with my life. now you may say "that's not a bad thing" well it makes my current life feel empty by comparison. now one could say 'oh change your life'. but i am 1) generally resistent to change and 2) actually quite content with my current life, at least most of the time. my overall view on this is that i think this desire is an unhealthy one, but i'm incapable of just, like, squashing it. do you have any advice

A: there's plusses and minuses to this. on the one hand it can lead to a lot of insanity and a very unfair and imbalanced worldview. HOWEVER, it also is maybe the most potent artistic fuel there could ever be. so there's that</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how has the corporatization of the current world affected your life?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 6:12 am

Q: how has the corporatization of the current world affected your life?

A: it doesnt feel like this has really changed during my lifetime</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you ever taught a 1 on 1 lesson? and would you ever be willing to teach a 1 on 1 lesson?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 6:45 am

Q: have you ever taught a 1 on 1 lesson? and would you ever be willing to teach a 1 on 1 lesson?

A: it's better if people just come to me for advice if they need it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to make music sheets</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 8:26 am

Q: how to make music sheets

A: take a look at as many of them as you can, while also knowing how the music sounds. compare how it sounds to how it looks, keep doing this for more and more pieces and before you know it you'll be fluent. pretty much the same way you learned to read and write in english, probably</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What's the difference between magic powers and super powers?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 12:02 pm

Q: What's the difference between magic powers and super powers?

A: they're both fictional tropes but also useful metaphors. couldnt really describe the difference other than just the way the words look and sound, whichever one you decide to use</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Have you ever been in a situation where you had a bunch of partway completed projects but just couldn't bring yourself to push them over the line to a state where they could be shared? I either move onto the next thing too quickly or just sit on my hands while they languish. Do you have any advice on how one gets themselves out of that situation and into the realm of completed works?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 12:09 pm

Q: Have you ever been in a situation where you had a bunch of partway completed projects but just couldn't bring yourself to push them over the line to a state where they could be shared? I either move onto the next thing too quickly or just sit on my hands while they languish. Do you have any advice on how one gets themselves out of that situation and into the realm of completed works?

A: this can be a lifetime endeavor. there's an unlimited number of different strategies you can use. if your desire to have completed works is strong enough, you will have no choice but to start doing some strategies. most of them are very simple, and just involve doing the stuff and finishing it, but if you have hangups and issues then it all comes down to whether the desire can overcome the hangups</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is arial the best font?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 1:01 pm

Q: is arial the best font?

A: no, but it's there</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>have you ever considered writing a musical?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 2:06 pm

Q: have you ever considered writing a musical?

A: almost all of my work is musical</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what do i do if i'm so anxious that i throw up and shake before every exam even though i've studied . it's the worst for oral exams, extremely evil type of activity</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 2:37 pm

Q: what do i do if i'm so anxious that i throw up and shake before every exam even though i've studied . it's the worst for oral exams, extremely evil type of activity

A: you'll learn something from this but hopefully you wont have to do it again after this phase of your life</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what was your reaction when you found out the sun was going to explode as a kid</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 2:45 pm

Q: what was your reaction when you found out the sun was going to explode as a kid

A: i dont recall finding out a sun-explosion is any kind of probable within any kind of timeframe anywhere near ours</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I have this crazy mental block with lyrics, where I feel like I'm incapable of judging them. I can't tell if they're good or not. I keep trying to think of what other people will think of them, and then I just get paralysis. How do i worry less about what other people will think of my music and lyrics, and learn to write for ME?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 4:06 pm

Q: I have this crazy mental block with lyrics, where I feel like I'm incapable of judging them. I can't tell if they're good or not. I keep trying to think of what other people will think of them, and then I just get paralysis. How do i worry less about what other people will think of my music and lyrics, and learn to write for ME?

A: what drew you towards music in the first place? have you had such experiences with music where the music touched and affected YOU deeply and personally? if so, then that's what it's all about, that's where you wanna go. If you've never had this, then..... well, ... have you ever had this? i'm guessing this must have happened at some point, to trigger your attraction towards music and desire to work with it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to stop someone from doing something without using punishments?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 4:07 pm

Q: how to stop someone from doing something without using punishments?

A: maybe you could make an offer they cant refuse</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Thoughts on February?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 4:23 pm

Q: Thoughts on February?

A: blink and you might miss it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if the universe is expanding at all points am i expanding too</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 5:16 pm

Q: if the universe is expanding at all points am i expanding too

A: i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do I start a timeline of everything that has happened since the beginning of human history</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 6:35 pm

Q: how do I start a timeline of everything that has happened since the beginning of human history

A: you'll probably never be able to discern exactly everything that's ever happened, so first you'll have to decide which re-tellings of the story youre going to be following and referencing, or if you're going to make your own</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if there's a great britain, does mean there's a little britain (and if there is, then where is it)?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 7:27 pm

Q: if there's a great britain, does mean there's a little britain (and if there is, then where is it)?

A: maybe great britain thinks of all the overseas territories as little britains</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i enjoy music a lot, ive even taught myself a bit of music theory, but i have found that the process of actually making music isn't something i enjoy very much. i can't tell if it just isn't for me or i just need to get past the initial discomfort around being bad at it. uuhhhh what do i do?? ?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 7:31 pm

Q: i enjoy music a lot, ive even taught myself a bit of music theory, but i have found that the process of actually making music isn't something i enjoy very much. i can't tell if it just isn't for me or i just need to get past the initial discomfort around being bad at it. uuhhhh what do i do?? ?

A: how about........ listening to music</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What's something you used to dislike but learned to like? Maybe I could learn to like it, if it's also something I dislike.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 8:25 pm

Q: What's something you used to dislike but learned to like? Maybe I could learn to like it, if it's also something I dislike.

A: i think it's important to ask yourself why you want to like the thing you dislike. who likes it, and are you trying to gain their favor.....</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What to do when I feel like I don't know what to do with my time?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 9:20 pm

Q: What to do when I feel like I don't know what to do with my time?

A: how about doing everything</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>You described yourself as being on a "bonkers lifepath." I like that description. In what way is it bonkers?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 9:50 pm

Q: You described yourself as being on a "bonkers lifepath." I like that description. In what way is it bonkers?

A: that was refering to the way it was described in the question you took that from</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What do you think animals would do if they had hands</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 11:02 pm

Q: What do you think animals would do if they had hands

A: pick things up</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Would you agree, that to know how small is too small, one would have to know how large is too large?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.14.26 11:07 pm

Q: Would you agree, that to know how small is too small, one would have to know how large is too large?

A: the implication here is that you are working with some size limits. but does a lower limit imply the existence of an upper limit? no it does not have to</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if blue was a color what color would it be</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 1:08 am

Q: if blue was a color what color would it be

A: a 'named' color. a color with a name</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you like the more personal questions better, or the more "What's your opinion on lampshades dominating the universe" type questions?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 2:32 am

Q: Do you like the more personal questions better, or the more "What's your opinion on lampshades dominating the universe" type questions?

A: every question is a new challenge, such as: to consder how many types of questions there are</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what fonts do you use?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 6:41 am

Q: what fonts do you use?

A: whatever i can get. sometimes i go nuts with different ones, other times i chill out and just use regular to let the words themselves do the talking</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to melody??</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 8:12 am

Q: how to melody??

A: the melody itself describes how, or at least one of the ways</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is it okay to hang a chair on a wall?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 8:52 am

Q: is it okay to hang a chair on a wall?

A: sure just dont make a habit of it</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Will you talk more about Steve in the future</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 10:14 am

Q: Will you talk more about Steve in the future

A: i will make more new things for you to wish i would talk more about</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is your favorite type of pasta, mine is the one where it goes long and good...</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 10:18 am

Q: what is your favorite type of pasta, mine is the one where it goes long and good...

A: there's this one called [not a sponsor] which i really like lately</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How can one handle both deeply meaningful, complicated tasks and mundane, boring ones?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 11:20 am

Q: How can one handle both deeply meaningful, complicated tasks and mundane, boring ones?

A: maybe you could switch them</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how does it make you feel when you see many people waiting with baited breath for your next upload?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 11:29 am

Q: how does it make you feel when you see many people waiting with baited breath for your next upload?

A: it's inspiring</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do i stop procrastinating and start writing my book?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 11:41 am

Q: How do i stop procrastinating and start writing my book?

A: might as well try to deny yourself the immense joys of writing for as long as possible</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you think ohio memes are still funny in 2026?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 2:37 pm

Q: do you think ohio memes are still funny in 2026?

A: i'll give you this much, "...in [year]" memes are still funny in ohio</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>One of my friends wants to start writing poems again but doesn't have any ideas. What prompts do you have?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 4:50 pm

Q: One of my friends wants to start writing poems again but doesn't have any ideas. What prompts do you have?

A: write something that could be the first poem that ever existed. also try to make it the worst if you can</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you keep lists of things to do, do they ever get big and do you have like a system or something for them</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 4:59 pm

Q: how do you keep lists of things to do, do they ever get big and do you have like a system or something for them

A: you could spend a whole lifetime trying different systems. heck, i'm trying some right now</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>If you could have any animal as a pet (even fictional), what would it be?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 5:19 pm

Q: If you could have any animal as a pet (even fictional), what would it be?

A: can i just have fiction as a pet</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the point of life to have a lot of sex and make a lot of money? If not what is it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 6:14 pm

Q: Is the point of life to have a lot of sex and make a lot of money? If not what is it?

A: imagine if there was an invention that had infinite different purposes. pretty cool, right, this invention has infinite meanings, infinite purposes, infinte ways it can be. infinite stories it can tell. that would be a pretty cool invention. these same qualities also apply to this 'life' thing you mentioned earlier</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you have such a unique thought process not only while answering these questions, but making music?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 10:09 pm

Q: how do you have such a unique thought process not only while answering these questions, but making music?

A: what you wanna do is go into 'settings' .....</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>You ever look up at the stars and wonder how many of them have aliens?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.15.26 10:44 pm

Q: You ever look up at the stars and wonder how many of them have aliens?

A: might ponder the difference between an alien and not an alien</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>when all the ppl in power have no soul but u keep taking their advice and it doesn't work for some reason</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 1:13 am

Q: when all the ppl in power have no soul but u keep taking their advice and it doesn't work for some reason

A: do you ever wonder if you would still have a soul if you were ever in power</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if you could have an extra one of anything what would it be</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 2:38 am

Q: if you could have an extra one of anything what would it be

A: i would do an extra song</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Did you study jazz in high school or college? I've noticed in your music that you use a lot of advanced things like tritone substitutions or a ton of extensions or dominant chords resolving unexpectedly. Or maybe you just grew up listening to jazz?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 3:38 am

Q: Did you study jazz in high school or college? I've noticed in your music that you use a lot of advanced things like tritone substitutions or a ton of extensions or dominant chords resolving unexpectedly. Or maybe you just grew up listening to jazz?

A: have you ever walked in the woods between ohio and indiana not been sure where ohio stops and indiana begins? the same thing happens to anyone who's heard or played enough different music in their life, you realize there is no actual or visible border between this thing you call 'jazz' and not that thing</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i want to peruse a career in screenwriting. can you give me an idea for a short film i could write? it can be as dumb or as serious as you want</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 6:37 am

Q: i want to peruse a career in screenwriting. can you give me an idea for a short film i could write? it can be as dumb or as serious as you want

A: you could just make it about me telling you what to write</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what are some changes you would've done to your rain poem in "when i get older", if you have any</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 9:30 am

Q: what are some changes you would've done to your rain poem in "when i get older", if you have any

A: "no changes, it's fine" ~ my poem about how the other poem is</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>favorite harry potter character ?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 12:26 pm

Q: favorite harry potter character ?

A: i can only think of one</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>hey bill i've been having internet issues with my computer for the past few days and your website is what i've been using to test if it works how does that make you feel?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 1:17 pm

Q: hey bill i've been having internet issues with my computer for the past few days and your website is what i've been using to test if it works how does that make you feel?

A: important</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What's the most subjectively boring thing you find interesting?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 3:34 pm

Q: What's the most subjectively boring thing you find interesting?

A: figuring out who gets to be the subject and who's the object, in these scenarios</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>bill i dont get standard deviation. Can you explain it to me</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 4:22 pm

Q: bill i dont get standard deviation. Can you explain it to me

A: "how close is close enough?" standard deviation tells this</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is insanity</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 5:18 pm

Q: what is insanity

A: it's one of those old television tropes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What's a pasta shape that doesnt exist yet, that you would like to see in the future?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 6:34 pm

Q: What's a pasta shape that doesnt exist yet, that you would like to see in the future?

A: 3 ring binder</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>would you rather have it so restaurants never get your order wrong or be buried alive on the exoplanet wasp-12b</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 6:34 pm

Q: would you rather have it so restaurants never get your order wrong or be buried alive on the exoplanet wasp-12b

A: let me think</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what's your hottest take about squids?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 6:35 pm

Q: what's your hottest take about squids?

A: the regular size squid is actually the giant. it's like a built in upsell, like they do at wendys sometimes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is an instrument you've wanted to learn, but haven't yet? Or do you know them all?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 7:18 pm

Q: What is an instrument you've wanted to learn, but haven't yet? Or do you know them all?

A: how about 'measured judgement'</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sometimes when i improv on the piano i kinda zone out like i'm not even aware that i'm playing, or daydreaming while i do this. Am i schizo???</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 8:05 pm

Q: Sometimes when i improv on the piano i kinda zone out like i'm not even aware that i'm playing, or daydreaming while i do this. Am i schizo???

A: that could just be your stage name</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you consider yourself to be wise or emotionally intelligent</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 8:21 pm

Q: do you consider yourself to be wise or emotionally intelligent

A: ah, this is one of those 'choose your own adventure' compliments</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What do you do when life gives you lemons?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 8:45 pm

Q: What do you do when life gives you lemons?

A: give life some melons in return</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Have you ever worn hard clothing and then Try to compensate by eating soft food</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 9:14 pm

Q: Have you ever worn hard clothing and then Try to compensate by eating soft food

A: i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how to inspire you self?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 9:22 pm

Q: how to inspire you self?

A: grab an ice cold [not a sponsor]</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what do i do if i'm scared every decision i make will cause something horrible</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 9:32 pm

Q: what do i do if i'm scared every decision i make will cause something horrible

A: you could start daydreaming about mathematics, for escapism</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i can really use some words of affirmation right now can you give some</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 9:42 pm

Q: i can really use some words of affirmation right now can you give some

A: it sounds like you're doing fine, but to be fair you didnt tell me whats wrong</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you like apples</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 9:42 pm

Q: do you like apples

A: not that much</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>would you rather eat sand or not eat sand</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 9:51 pm

Q: would you rather eat sand or not eat sand

A: how about apples</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what inspires you to get out of bed on those days when you really don't feel like it ??</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 10:01 pm

Q: what inspires you to get out of bed on those days when you really don't feel like it ??

A: what inspires life to exist</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>I want to be rich but I also hate rich people. What do I do?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 10:20 pm

Q: I want to be rich but I also hate rich people. What do I do?

A: you'll have to become the world's first likeable rich person</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what are your thoughts on marching bands? if you don't have any thoughts on the topic, then what was your most recent breakfast?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 10:28 pm

Q: what are your thoughts on marching bands? if you don't have any thoughts on the topic, then what was your most recent breakfast?

A: i had a marching breakfast</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i've been full of love and poetry and colors and magic lately, is there something wrong with that?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.16.26 10:39 pm

Q: i've been full of love and poetry and colors and magic lately, is there something wrong with that?

A: now that you mention it, it could be a cover up for something</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>when there's so many questions you want to ask, but not enough time/space to ask all of them, how do you go about picking the best question to ask?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 12:17 am

Q: when there's so many questions you want to ask, but not enough time/space to ask all of them, how do you go about picking the best question to ask?

A: how do i pick how to answer</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How come lies can make a song feel more honest</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 12:38 am

Q: How come lies can make a song feel more honest

A: if the words are wrong then they instantly get out of the way and reveal how truthful the music is</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>why is life so beautiful?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 1:14 am

Q: why is life so beautiful?

A: could be defective</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Are we gonna get rapid fire release of songs/projects when you've got a few saved up, or a trickle.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 1:52 am

Q: Are we gonna get rapid fire release of songs/projects when you've got a few saved up, or a trickle.

A: there will be a lot</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>favorite radiohead song?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 1:56 am

Q: favorite radiohead song?

A: the happy one</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Does the order of numbers make sense?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 3:40 am

Q: Does the order of numbers make sense?

A: yes it does</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the color orange named after the fruit or the other way around?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 4:07 am

Q: Is the color orange named after the fruit or the other way around?

A: orange fruit was first</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When will we run out of atoms</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 4:27 am

Q: When will we run out of atoms

A: that all depends on whether or not it's possible to recycle the atom</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you believe in the idea of genres of music</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 5:16 am

Q: Do you believe in the idea of genres of music

A: i guess it all depends how much fun you want to have</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>you ever think about stuff?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 5:41 am

Q: you ever think about stuff?

A: that's exactly what distracted me from giving a better answer than this</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i want to make lists of things to do and i will start in some way or another BUT i never finish doing it in that particular method because i get carried away thinking about other ways to do it. so instead of doing things, i spend a lot of time thinking about 'how to do lists to do things'. And it drives me crazy!! because when i eventually start doing stuff and the momentum is going, everything is great. is there any way i could just do things more consistently? how do i hack my brain to do that</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 6:49 am

Q: i want to make lists of things to do and i will start in some way or another BUT i never finish doing it in that particular method because i get carried away thinking about other ways to do it. so instead of doing things, i spend a lot of time thinking about 'how to do lists to do things'. And it drives me crazy!! because when i eventually start doing stuff and the momentum is going, everything is great. is there any way i could just do things more consistently? how do i hack my brain to do that

A: it may be possible that the consistency is already fine, youre just sometimes having a confidence problem where youre worried that the consistency isnt good enough. creative success is exactly like weather patterns</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>thoughts on february's calendar looking like a 7x4 rectangle if your week starts on sunday? next year it'll look like that if your week starts on monday!</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 7:59 am

Q: thoughts on february's calendar looking like a 7x4 rectangle if your week starts on sunday? next year it'll look like that if your week starts on monday!

A: this is why february often inspires the urge to learn how the rest of the calendar year is lined up. learn the basics, like apr==jul, sep==dec, which is a gateway to then start looking into the 28 year cycle of leap patterns, etc depending on what size can of worms you ordered</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is it that the least funny thing you can do is try to be funny?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 8:08 am

Q: Why is it that the least funny thing you can do is try to be funny?

A: did you not expect being funny to have funny rules</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How to stop consuming media and instead create my own. The urge to start is killing me but I can't bring myself to start for some reason.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 11:05 am

Q: How to stop consuming media and instead create my own. The urge to start is killing me but I can't bring myself to start for some reason.

A: you're craving a creative outlet. it's only a matter of time before you find something you enjoy</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>did you use random scenes in the music video for "if the world doesn't end"? I feel like the visuals have less continuity in this one</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 11:07 am

Q: did you use random scenes in the music video for "if the world doesn't end"? I feel like the visuals have less continuity in this one

A: yes you are right, i pillaged my archive of test scenes and used 70% of them</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Are things different than they always have been</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 12:43 pm

Q: Are things different than they always have been

A: it's always a blend of similar and different. that is the chef's promise</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HEY BILL, WOULD YOU CONSIDER YOURSLEF TO BE A [[BIG SHOT!!!]??</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 1:15 pm

Q: HEY BILL, WOULD YOU CONSIDER YOURSLEF TO BE A [[BIG SHOT!!!]??

A: that sounds like a halloween costume</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you think the song 'Rain Rain Go Away' offends people who like rain?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 1:27 pm

Q: do you think the song 'Rain Rain Go Away' offends people who like rain?

A: i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>are floors just sideways walls that we walk on, or are walls just sideways floors that separate different rooms?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 1:38 pm

Q: are floors just sideways walls that we walk on, or are walls just sideways floors that separate different rooms?

A: it really all depends on the direction of gravity</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you like sports?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 2:38 pm

Q: do you like sports?

A: i appreciate that it's possible for either team to win</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>In two friends on the beach, he says, "I think I'm going to take the friendship picture," and later, "thanks for coming with me I usually buy terrible pictures unless when you're here I buy the good ones" or something which would imply that he bought the picture. But he doesn't take the picture with him. So did he buy it or not? and if he did, why did he not take it, let alone pay money for it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 3:22 pm

Q: In two friends on the beach, he says, "I think I'm going to take the friendship picture," and later, "thanks for coming with me I usually buy terrible pictures unless when you're here I buy the good ones" or something which would imply that he bought the picture. But he doesn't take the picture with him. So did he buy it or not? and if he did, why did he not take it, let alone pay money for it?

A: it was my impression that he whispered it to the person at the podium, who is to make arrangements for the purchase and delivery. it's one of those high brow kind of places, despite its average retail storefront</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you think the world has been getting better or worse over these past few years?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 5:06 pm

Q: do you think the world has been getting better or worse over these past few years?

A: i have absolutely no way to properly measure this, but, for reference, it's always been popular (at any time, ever) to say it's getting worse. which strongly hints to me that it is at worst approximately the same</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Programming is an interesting thing. There are moments where I feel like nothing makes sense and my world is ending and I don't know shit and I should just give up... and then I figure it out and create the this and I feel the most fulfilled I've ever been in my life and I can do fucking anything and my ego grows to gargantuan heights.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 6:07 pm

Q: Programming is an interesting thing. There are moments where I feel like nothing makes sense and my world is ending and I don't know shit and I should just give up... and then I figure it out and create the this and I feel the most fulfilled I've ever been in my life and I can do fucking anything and my ego grows to gargantuan heights.

A: ah, the circle of life</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>are you a different person 50% of the time</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 7:23 pm

Q: are you a different person 50% of the time

A: not entirely</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Have you had poetry in the mind recently?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 7:59 pm

Q: Have you had poetry in the mind recently?

A: THERE'S A TIME AND PLACE FOR POETRY and that time is sometimes</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>people are always sitting down and sitting up, but have you ever tried to sit sideways?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 8:09 pm

Q: people are always sitting down and sitting up, but have you ever tried to sit sideways?

A: yes i have</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>is it possible to be too ambitious?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 8:38 pm

Q: is it possible to be too ambitious?

A: ambition itself is what stretches its own limits, so it would be a sketchy thing to try to measure</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>But how do i pull a habit out of a rat?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 8:45 pm

Q: But how do i pull a habit out of a rat?

A: rehab</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how should i stay consistent making art? do i even need to be consistent?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 8:54 pm

Q: how should i stay consistent making art? do i even need to be consistent?

A: sometimes getting this right means getting it wrong. i'm sorry if that sounds confusing, but it turns out that's how it stays interesting</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What is your favorite number that isn't in 9 8 7?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 9:14 pm

Q: What is your favorite number that isn't in 9 8 7?

A: how about the square root of 2, except i might have snuck that in there</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do you organize your notes? I'd like to start writing things in notes as well and wonder how to organize them so they don't get cluttered</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 10:56 pm

Q: how do you organize your notes? I'd like to start writing things in notes as well and wonder how to organize them so they don't get cluttered

A: have you tried putting them all in the exact same place</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How much of what you write on the questions forum do you remember after you write it?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.17.26 11:50 pm

Q: How much of what you write on the questions forum do you remember after you write it?

A: how much of your life do you think you remember, sorry for deflecting, i was accidentally holding a mirror</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what tracks do you usually record first</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 12:28 am

Q: what tracks do you usually record first

A: the craziest</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>if you had to make a league for somehting, like the NBA or the NHL, what would it be?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 2:35 am

Q: if you had to make a league for somehting, like the NBA or the NHL, what would it be?

A: has anyone ever tried putting all those sports leagues in a league, like a sports association or something</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is your favorite word</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 5:10 am

Q: what is your favorite word

A: thank goodness to the 'time' dimension, which allows us to favor new words at different times. it's the only way to live, or at least it's the only way i know how to live. that being said, at this moment my favorite word is 'poij' but not anymore</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>how do i fix my cycle of thinking that im useless and not contributing to society, then being sad and therefore not contributing to society because im too sad to do so</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 6:11 am

Q: how do i fix my cycle of thinking that im useless and not contributing to society, then being sad and therefore not contributing to society because im too sad to do so

A: first if you can just sort of identify that that mental cycle is a bit defective/faulty, but then, most importantly, just start doing something else interesting you can focus on, and get interested by</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>do you think the song in your music videos is more meaningful than the video, or vice versa?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 6:40 am

Q: do you think the song in your music videos is more meaningful than the video, or vice versa?

A: in a song video, the song must be able to work without the video. and the video almost certainly does NOT work without the song, but the video must also work well enough with the song so as not to ruin the song. in otherwords the video must work very very well with the song also</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>thoughts on one-word questions (e.g. what?)</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 7:05 am

Q: thoughts on one-word questions (e.g. what?)

A: a timeless classic. now that i think about it, it's likely that these sorts of expressions were among the very first 'words' to ever exist</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>¿What's your thought on the upside down question mark?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 11:37 am

Q: ¿What's your thought on the upside down question mark?

A: it's used in spanish just the way you just used it, but in a non-spanish language it can be a great indicator of extreme confusion</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what emotions do you assign to each color?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 1:05 pm

Q: what emotions do you assign to each color?

A: emotions are impossible to describe exactly. not even with words, or colors</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what is the meaning of life?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 2:10 pm

Q: what is the meaning of life?

A: regardless of whether you choose it or it chooses you, there are many many many choices, often simultaneously</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Say you have a really basic bass line. It's going C G A F, staying in key. You start jamming away with a little twiddly synth solo, and you want your solo to go non-diatonic, and hit those lovely in between notes. In those brief moments that your synth is non-diatonic, do you adjust the bass for that moment to match whatever key the synth is temporarily in? Like if the synth hits a C# while the bass is playing its G, should you change the bass to G# so they sound like they're in the same key? What about when borrowing an entire chord from another key, change the bass to match or let the bass keep going about it's business?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 3:39 pm

Q: Say you have a really basic bass line. It's going C G A F, staying in key. You start jamming away with a little twiddly synth solo, and you want your solo to go non-diatonic, and hit those lovely in between notes. In those brief moments that your synth is non-diatonic, do you adjust the bass for that moment to match whatever key the synth is temporarily in? Like if the synth hits a C# while the bass is playing its G, should you change the bass to G# so they sound like they're in the same key? What about when borrowing an entire chord from another key, change the bass to match or let the bass keep going about it's business?

A: you bring up a whole series of unanswerable questions. maybe listing them will help, as a thought experiment. scenario 1: youre the synth player, playing along to a recorded track which you cant change. is the synth player 'allowed' to ever play out of key? (yes you are allowed, but what does it sound like? try it and find out) scenario 2: youre the bass player, playing along to a recording with the synth solo already on it which you cant change, but let's say you already know the track and you know when it's going to go out of key. Are you allowed to make special accomodations in the bass? will that make it sound too much like you knew the seemingly improvised solo too well? scenario 3: the bass and synth are both being played simultaneously live by 2 different people, and the solo is being improvised. to what extent can the bass accomodate in real time what is happening? however...... despite all these words, no one is learning anything until sound starts being made</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>what are you thinking about?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 5:18 pm

Q: what are you thinking about?

A: how to answer this</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How do you change your way of thinking? How do you make your brain think differently? Is it possible to do so through effort alone?</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2.18.26 6:07 pm

Q: How do you change your way of thinking? How do you make your brain think differently? Is it possible to do so through effort alone?

A: whatever you are surrounded with, whatever things you see hear and say, those will start to become the language of your thinking</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>