<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Bill Wurtz – Questions</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>Unofficial RSS feed for Bill Wurtz questions page</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>8:43 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What do you think about the Swiffer Sweepers?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; back in my day we had to swiff and sweep with two seperate devices &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 7:05 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Is jazz stupid?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; out of context it's not really possible to know what is meant by the word jazz &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 6:54 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; you ever try makin a grilled cheese in a pan with oaxaca cheese&amp;nbsp;&amp; sharp cheddar in it? and squashin some garlic cloves and getting the butter all toasty with the garlic cloves, and adding honey, chili powder, rosemary, and thyme into the butter in the pan? life could be a dream&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no i have not tried exactly those steps &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 5:38 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What is the rabbit's name from your most recent video?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; the rabbit &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 4:38 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; best use of a swear word in a song?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i'll have to hear all the songs first to know for sure &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 4:20 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Do you think "music for musicians" is more accurately "music for autistic musicians"&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no i dont believe so &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 3:41 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; You said in a recent answer to a question that you've never really found an artist that you can "trust wholeheartedly and fully". I'm curious about what you mean by this...As in, you have never found an artist who you can always count on for making works that connect with you, that you appreciate in some way or another...? &lt;/qco&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;sure, that sounds about right&lt;h3&gt;&lt;qco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Do you aim to be an artist that people can "trust wholeheartedly"?&lt;/qco&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;of course that's what i'd be going for, but i also recognize based on my own experience that that's a ridiculously tall order. considering no one has ever completely done this for me. but for fleeting moments it sure feels like it &lt;h3&gt;&lt;qco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Do you think this is even an achievable goal that artists should strive for?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;it would be none of my business to tell other people what they should or shouldn't strive for</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 10:16 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is the meaning of life to you&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>it's indescribable except for the fact that everything ever done or said describes it &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 9:48 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; 'falseth' needs to be a word similarly to 'truth' im tired of saying 'falsehood'&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; sometimes it's called a "lie", sometimes it's called a "myth", if you're really in a special mood you can call it a "fib" &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 9:33 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Why are some people confused and sometimes even mildly offended when I affirm to them that I enjoy solitude? Also 'Fly Around' is a certified banger just thought you should know.&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i dont really have an answer to this, except to make more music which you can enjoy listening to alone &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 9:11 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you try hard to make it look easy and if so, do you wish otherwise&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; neither</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>12:17 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What do you think of this poem I wrote? &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;PLEASE GOD HELP IM SCARED &lt;br/&gt;PLEASE GOD HELP ME IM SCARED &lt;br/&gt;PLEASE GOD HELP ME IM SCARED &lt;br/&gt;WHATS GOING ON &lt;br/&gt;WHATS HAPPENING IM SCARED &lt;br/&gt;WHATS GOING ON IM SCARED &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; great. very strong, clear, almost feels like a satire of the 'poem' format, which feels well deserved and well executed &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 11:56 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; why do people ponder the "meaning of life" and never stop to ask themself what the hell kinda loaded question is that. it was nobody's choice to put us here, there is no reason, we just have to deal with it. sorry i was just saying what was on my mind what are your thoughts on the meaning of life?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i think it's a ridiculous question for totally different reasons than you. to me what you said is also ridiculous. for me the ridiculousness about the "the meaning of life" thing is that it makes it sound like there is supposed to be 1 meaning and purpose for everyone at all times. but the way it seems to me is that there are infinite meanings all the time. new ones, old ones, it's endless. literally everything is meaningful. meaning is inescapable. even little pockets of what may seem like 'meaninglessness' only elevates the surrounding meanings &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.7.26&amp;nbsp; 11:32 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Should I do a bad thing today?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; maybe some other time</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>4:26 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is the cube root of pi?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; a little less than 1 and a half &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 3:17 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; i feel like i lost the recipes should i go through an intensive memory lane session or bang rocks and hope i get a spark of familiarity or start a new big or something else or all of em?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; those all sound like fine strategies &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 2:52 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; how uis all of your music so good i just listened to like 30 fucking songs from you while playing minecraft at 1 am and it was an ethereal experience&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; good heavens, it's my target audience</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>9:01 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you have a favourite dinosaur? If so, which one is it?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; maybe if any of them werent so freakin extinct &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 8:21 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; potato&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; thank you for writing potato here &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 7:58 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Thoughts on 9?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; plays some really cool games with digits, in base 10. this is normal for a number one less than the base number &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp;6:01 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; I'm gonna write my master's thesis this year and last year when I wrote my bachelors thesis this one guy was my thesis supervisor because he was the only professor at our university that had knowledge of the methods I was using. and then after that his wife birthed twins so he was on parental leave for a while. but I heard from a different professor that he will still want to be my supervisor for my masters thesis even though he is partly on leave. but he never told me that himself I just heard that from a different professor. and just yesterday we had our first thesis seminar where we discussed some things about everyone's theses and what they're gonna be like and what the process is gonna be but my supervisor-to-be wasn't there because it was Wednesday and he doesn't work Wednesdays &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;so one of the professors that were there told me to email the professor that wasn't there to schedule a meeting to talk about my thesis with him. so I sent the email but now I'm scared that he never wanted to be my supervisor this year to begin with and that it was all a huge miscommunication and that he's gonna find my email really weird and that will be so embarrassing. I'm so nervous&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(nods understandingly)</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>9:40 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what's that movie where its like war on the stars&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; dune</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>3:01 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; ever walked on top of a big gray square?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 1:39 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; did you ever wonder what you were gonna do in life&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;as a kid?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes but i also did things in life then &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 1:26 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what's yur opinion on the concept of humans wanting to understand everything?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; dont you think it would make for such fantastic dinner table conversation &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 12:32 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Which of the planets of the solar system is spinning on its 'side', compared to all the other planets?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; uranus maybe but i'm not totally sure &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 11:38 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; A lot of the times I feel like I have no will over anything at all. It's all either predetermined or random. Am I crazy for thinking this way?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no but i also dont think it's true &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 10:45 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; I love the expert mode of this site, but it seems to me that it's also simple mode. Do you agree?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no, people often struggle to understand exactly what does and does not go on there</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>7:27 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; ignoring cultural overuse and misappropriation, do you think that swear words (specifically the F and S words,) are phonetically pleasing? For example, the "Phuh" sound followed by a strong "Kh" allows for a great release of air in the word, affording the speaker a lot of satisfaction from saying the word. Does this seem accurate? also second question favorite swear word?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; like any kind of aesthetics, it can be impossible to say what's pleasing and not, because it has so much to do with what's been seen or heard before and after &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 6:46 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; The power of music is mystical and boundless. I'm ashamed to admit it, but my heart is frozen in bitterness, resentment, anger, and hate, but today, while listening to a song, I felt a glimmer of hope. I can't even tell you what the words were;&amp;nbsp;it was mostly a feeling, but it changed my perspective ever so slightly, in a completely unexpected moment. Isn't music amazing? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes, music is magic &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 6:34 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you have a least favorite dinosaur maybe&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 6:07 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; I am ten thousand years old&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i want to believe you &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 4:53 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Why did 7 eat 9? What did 9 do to 7?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; nothing, that's just wordplay in english &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 4:15 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Do you follow&amp;nbsp;&amp; participate in a religion at all?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; over time i seem to find that word more and more defective &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 4:04 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; hello is this the post office&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no i dont believe so</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>10:36 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Does making your music sound older make it fresher&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; this becomes increasingly true if you are cross pollinating from multiple different times and places &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 9:47 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you like when people send you their art via this page? if so, do you enjoy being shown specific things, and/or do you prefer to be left to explore a larger archive on your own? i find that i don't usually enjoy specific songs people send me, but when i check out the rest of an artists work..... now that's when the real fun happens&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it can be very awkward for someone to individually and directly show another person something they made. the perception and response is going to be inseparably wrapped up in the relationship of those two people. now that i think about it there's nothing wrong with that &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 9:26 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Is Sonic's last name The Hedgehog?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 9:23 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What should I do if everything is stupid and always has been&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; write about your stupid feelings &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 8:17 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; How do you feel about that species of snail that does photosynthesis by nabbing chlorophyll from eating plants?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; never heard of it &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 7:44 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; how many licks does it take to get to the center of a tootsie pop?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i'd be more concerned with how many it takes to get out</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>11:23 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Why don't you make more videos?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it's not as easy as you think, to make them. it probably is easy for other people, but not for me. the reason for this is quite simply because i'm crazy. i used to have some more logical explanations for it, but then i later realized i was wrong and i no longer know the reason. and the reason i thought those reasons were correct before is because i'm crazy, which is also the reason that i don't actually know the reason. That being said, getting back to your original question i'm always making more videos &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 11:16 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; i realized that pretty much internalize everything other people say and i don't know how to navigate that&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; maybe there's some way you could send it back out &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 11:12 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is the cultural significance of Comic Sans?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; one day it turned up on Windows as one of the default fonts. it seems as though everyone fell in love with it so fast that it became so overused so fast that everyone got so sick of it so fast that it became a joke. but the font is still good, and so is the joke. so it's like a 2-in-1 &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 9:19 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is something novel you have partaked in recently&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; cubic numbers, for example &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 8:46 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; You mentioned once anout your "Piece of Garbage" videos that they came from an exercise on how you felt at some point in your life's calender. Are there any other songs or videos you tried this for?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes, the majority of the short jingles starting from july 7, 2015 are probably part of this &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 7:59 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Does hand size matter when playing an instrument?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; sometimes but it's usually not the most important thing &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 7:21 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is your favourite number between 0 and 10&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; oh what the heck, 5 &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 6:32 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; is there anything that's been overlooked in your work that you haven't had the chance to mention?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; probably, but i can't be sure because i don't know exactly what every individual person has seen &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 4:44 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Is the media the enemy of the people?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; media is the enemy of other media with an opposing worldview &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 4:09 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What's your opinion on refrigerators being invented as a response to frigerators?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; not true &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 3:28 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; help! i am in constant awe at the beauty of this world but there is not enough energy in my body to canvas it into art! this kills me!!&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i know it feels that way, but this is exactly what energizes your work. it's energized your question for sure &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 1:52 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; oh, my memories are coming back in ways that i wasn't ready for, but i'm still enjoying the way it feels&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; thank you for saying that lyric here. it's very helpful &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 1:27 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you like playing basketball?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; seems like fun but i've barely done it &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 1:17 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; so i was making coffee. had to wash a mug because i don't trust my family to do it yk. so i was out here using soap, making sure the hot water washes off any grime on every part of the mug. but then i realised after a long time of washing it that i didn't get a tea spoon. do you know how much faster it would have been if i washed the tea spoon with the mug?? so i grabbed a tea spoon and it had an uncomfortable amount of food on it, despite having just come out of the dishwasher. i try using hot water and soap, hoping the pressure of the water will be enough to wash the food off but nah i had to use something. sadly that something had to be my hands because i don't trust the sponge. i'd use gloves but we don't have any for some reason. so i have to wash my hands after that. so now i can make coffee, yeah? i put the coffee stuff in, pour hot water and go to the fridge where i saw before a bottle of milk. i grab the bottle of milk and apparently someone thought a drop of milk is enough to do anything with cause i check it and it's empty. literally nothing. that has never happened to me before. i had to drink black coffee cause i already brewed the thing&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; now that's what i call storytelling &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 12:44 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Is there a point which one can expect to find the balance between giving a crap and not doing so on the creative journey?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; these two forces will probably always be toying with each other. actually probably if either one of them wins, the show stops &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 12:23 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; should i adopt a ferret?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; sure. or get adopted by a ferret &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 12:18 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What's your thoughts on rats? Like the little guys that killed a third of Europe and fight over bagels&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; how could i dare upstage the thoughts that you've just brought to the table &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 11:43 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what makes something meaningful&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; anything can make something meaningful. there is no limit to the mechanics of this &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 11:16 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; should I take a personal loan to get out of my parents house&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; has anyone offered you one &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 11:08 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; does having an answer always imply there was a question to begin with?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; not exactly &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 11:03 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; probably has been asked before but, aside from the likely technical difficulties of performing live given the range of instruments you use and the fact most of them are random electronic sounds not entirely bound to physical instruments, would you ever consider doing a live concert? In a hypothetical scenario where you were able to perform everything live using say, a ridiculous amount of synths and/or soundboards, or some other sort of device. Perhaps with funky lighting that takes you on an equally epic journey as the visuals of your music videos do. Would you do it?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; the problems with doing a live show are completely different from the ones you mentioned. if a live show happens it's going to be a band of human ass beings playing in an ensemble of somewhere between 4 and 12 instruments. normal instruments like the ones you see in most bands. and i have a strict rule of no backing tracks and no video &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.8.26&amp;nbsp; 10:47 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what are your top 5 instruments as ranked by silly factor&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; clarinet, clarinet, clarinet, clarinet, clarinet, clarinet, sorry whoops i accidentally gave you the top 6</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>12:29 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; the fire alarm just went off in my school &lt;br/&gt;was it a real fire?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; USUALLY not, but it still might be &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 12:01 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What to do when you're bored&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; how about writing a book</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>5:01 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what's the longest word you can think of right now&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 'cat' oh no sorry 'cats' &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 3:05 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; could you answer this question with just blank&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no but i sometimes answer different questions that way. ones that don't ask me to do it &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 1:50 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Ever shook hands with a dog?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>10:13 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; How do you deal with feeling avoidant?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; probably avoid it &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 10:12 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; where did you learn how to play the drums &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;i noticed in the im a princess video that you play traditional grip (jazz grip? idk dude nobody knows what to call it)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; at home, and in the work place &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 9:25 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; If you could invent a new color, what would you call it?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 'could' &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 9:24 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you think I will ever be free?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes and no &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 8:52 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What's the newest thing in history?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; you asking this &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 8:46 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What is your favorite "key" on a keyboard?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; there would be no music if an argument didnt begin about which key to favor on a moment to moment basis &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp; 8:15 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Is lust even real, or is it just love society doesn't like?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it seems like it's not even a word people really use, except when comparing it to the word 'love'. you almost never see the word 'lust' used without the word 'love', so it's hard to get a feel for what the word actually means on its own, outside of that context</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.9.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>11:22 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; im really scared of ai especially since im young and music and art is a big part of my life. do you think it's plausible that ai blows us all to smithereens&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; what exactly is a smithereen</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>1:06 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; best kind of cheese?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; terrible, terrible cheese &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 12:32 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Which is easier to understand: quantum mechanics or quantum physics?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i dont think i actually understand the difference</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>i would but i dont know them all</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 1:19 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Have you ever incorrectly answered a question that has a correct answer on purpose? &lt;/qco&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;sure, i've tried that&lt;h3&gt;&lt;qco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I'm surprised by how accurately you answer some of these language, logic, and mathematics questions being asked here.&lt;/qco&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;honestly, answering 'correctly' a lot makes it more valuable and refreshing to occasionally make something up. And, in turn, making up a lot of answers makes it more valuable and refreshing to suddenly tell the cold hard truth out of nowhere&lt;h3&gt;&lt;qco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; How much time do you spend researching the questions, or do you perhaps already know the answers?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;i occasionally do research, but i usually do not</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>be and be not cause</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 1:22 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Do you think of every human on earth when you release content?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>6:44 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; how do you come up with so many non-answers that somehow also make sense?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; as soon as the teacher told us about 'artistic license,' i immediately skipped school and went out and got one and i've been renewing it daily ever since, just in case &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 6:42 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; how do I escape my overwhelmingly complex mind&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; you probably cant escape it but you can use it to your advantage. write down what youre feeling and thinking. other people may find it dazzling &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 5:31 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; I don't know why but this site was in my dream last night and you somehow found my number and told me you would make more music, is this a prophecy ?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i'm making more music but that was already true. i've also said that here many times before &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 4:56 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Mr. Wurtz, what is your favorite spatial dimension? And why?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 1 &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 3:03 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; pluto the (dwarf)planet is still cool right?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes but it's hard to know what it's really like because it's so far away &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 1:46 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; why do they call it oven when you of in the cold food of out hot eat the food?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2:25 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; thoughts on the estimated sign&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8494;?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i dont think i've ever seen that before &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 1:33 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What is the word that you use the least (but still use)?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; that would have to be a tie between many different words, because there are many different words i've only used once. and when i use them i usually act surprised (because i actually am) and i mention "... and i think that's the first time i've ever used that word before" &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 1:20 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what have you been thinking about lately?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; as usual, you will find out all about it later &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 12:47 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Why do I care so much about what others think of me?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; because on some level you know that they are just as important as you. the twist here is that they are also wondering what you think of them. which means, at the same time, you are just as important as them &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 12:22 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; thoughts on 67?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 1005 &amp;divide; 15 &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 11:42 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; if plants could think, what would they think about&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; what do you think about &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 10:18 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; where is kentucky&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; next to tennessee &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 9:35 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What is your favorite animal themed saying or figure of speech?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; how about woof &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 7:55 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you think it's important to actively do good things, donating, volunteering, helping people, etc. or do you think it's good enough to just not do bad things?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; you'll probably never even discover all the different good and bad ways to be &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 6:58 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what type of building does out to lunch take place&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; octagonal, that's for sure &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 5:29 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Out of all the songs that you've made, which would you say took the longest?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; maybe "i'm scared" &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 5:17 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Im going to try to become a pilot. How do you fly?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i'm not really sure &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 3:09 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Do you think it is likely that I am a fish?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 2:53 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; thoughts on number 3 being the number of perceivable dimensions for us humans&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; "it's worth a try" &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 2:33 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Do u think of a sus chord as the VI chord over the V-Basstone or just as a bunch of individual suspensions that all have their own significance? Sorry, my english is not the yellow from the egg &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i dont think of it either of those two ways. if music is going well, i'm feeling not thinking. if i'm 'thinking' too much then it means i need to take a break and come back when i'm in a more appropriate mood &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 2:18 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; why is everything so dumb and stupid?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; due to intelligence &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 2:06 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; how does everything work&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; everything works the same way, but i realize that's not a very useful answer &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 1:09 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; would you ever be open to having your work be featured in an exhibit somewhere?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; every time i walk through a museum with modern things in it i say "dammit, who are these people and why arent i in here", but then i remember i have been asked to have my work featured in museums and i apparently say no every time &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 12:29 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; when i listen to your music, i keep forgetting how good/important the percussion actually is. obviously the drums aren't the central point of the song but i keep being surprised by how good they feel to listen to and how much better they make the song. how do you usually go about drum programming?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it's not programmed it's played, but it's based on my musical instinct from years of experience. similar to the way you use the words you use when you speak &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 11:49 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; i've been reading up on wolves recently and i think they're cool. what do you think about wolves? do you think i can be a cool wolf if i really want to. thoughts or advice?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; you're way ahead of me on this topic &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 11:46 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Does working on your art and music feel different these days compared to a few years ago? Like the pressure, production stages, etc. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Do you prefer it?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; in some ways it always gets harder, but then it eventually becomes impossible and that always opens up a brand new door for it to become much easier. this cycle continues &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 10:35 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; i realized in the hi im steve vid when not steve is talking about the mountain and in the history of the world when talking about singled cell organisms under water the music you chose was very similar between the 2 situations. what would you say your musical inspiration is for this musical texture thing that you use from your musical texture pallet thing is? &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;happy new year btw &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; the music was done after the video, so in my case the music is inspired by what's happening in the video. the reason they sound similar is because.... well..... i'm still me &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 9:59 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; all words without meaning actually have one, and they refer to themselves. e.g: "life means nothing" = "life means nothing", but "flubglub means nothing" = "the word 'flubglub' means nothing". do you agree?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; sure but this is only scratching the surface of where meaning can be found &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 9:41 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; why is spacebar the universally accepted jump button in videogames?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; because jumping is important and it's the biggest button &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 8:48 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is your favourite tetris piece?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; that all depends on the current landscape on the ground &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 8:16 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Where can I buy someone's soul?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; that's actually impossible &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 7:55 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Do you like hot chocolate and if so do you have a favourite kind?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it's too hot for me &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 6:58 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; going to try picking up woodcarving. any suggestions for what I should carve?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; you probably wont know until you start carving and see how it feels &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.10.26&amp;nbsp; 6:57 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; remember that time when __________&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes, that's happened many times</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>7:37 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What type of question do you like answering more? questions about your content or questions about anything else.&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; the natural variation and variety is cherished. as in nature &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 6:00 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Do you think bad art is worse than no art?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; not necessarily, but it's also impossible to define either of those &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 4:48 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; I've heard of people who give the advice, "Be yourself", but is it truly possible to be anyone other than yourself?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i see your point, and i see that that makes it kind of an empty phrase. which is probably why i try to avoid using it &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 4:47 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Hi Bill ! &lt;br/&gt;I was forced to play piano as a child but had to learn on my own, no classes or teachers. Obviously that didnt work very well and just made me resentful of music and piano in general. I could play basic chords with a bass octave on the left hand, but no sheet music, no inversions, no scales, no music theory etc. &lt;br/&gt;Some years back, music found its way back into my heart and i want to learn piano again. &lt;br/&gt;Could you give me some advice on how i could approach it?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; the advice i always give is you have to make it your own. although you have an interesting situation because you actually did it on your own before. this is the way i would recommend, but i think the huge difference boils down to the fact that someone else wanted you to do it. so in that case you should be all set now. whatever excites you &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 3:09 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; favorite guitar capo placement&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; who knows, 3rd</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;i should also mention it's quite often that brand new level 0s come at me out of nowhere s</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 2:56 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do horses speak to you sometimes?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no i dont believe so &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 2:27 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; if i don't know everything that i dont know but i know that i dont know everything does that mean that i know everything without being smart&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it's going to give you some philosophical confidence. which can turn out both nice and not nice &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 1:32 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you actually like to wear soft clothing (cuz it makes it feel like you're rough in comparison)?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 1:14 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; How many owls do you need to see in a short period before you start thinking something is weird?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; that really depends where you are and where the owls are. there are perfectly normal places to see lots of owls &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 12:27 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; hoq so i stop being a liar&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; step one is finding the truth. that's really the hardest part &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 12:00 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Is the US to the east or west of russia&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; both, and also to the north and south and vice versa &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 11:53 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; thoughts on alchemy?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; seems legit &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 10:22 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; You are like the genie of answering questions (?)&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; my only answer to this is to go ahead and respond to this question with an answer &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 9:48 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you get musical ideas when you're about to fall asleep. i think you got might quit from a dream or that it was in your head when you woke up but do you ever get ideas in hypnagogia&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes, avalanches of things come at me when i'm halfway asleep. certainly not all of them are useful</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>6:21 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; How is doubt different from uncertainty&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; the word 'doubt' probably is more like youre leaning toward 'no' about something. but the word 'uncertainty' is probably less specific. it probably just means you dont know. Which makes me realize i think people probably use 'uncertain' to almost mean 'doubtful' and if you think about it that probably doesnt seem fair, from a linguistic standpoint. but as always there's surely way weirder atrocities just around the next corner, in the lagnuage &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 5:26 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; the last line of one of the projects you're working on will contain the letter A.&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; but how much exactly constitutes a 'line' &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 4:22 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; hey! I'm in the process of reinventing the way I write music and I'm curious where you start your writing process. What do you typically start with when writing music?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i start with what level of update i want to be working on. For example: if i'm working on update level zero, i'll come up with some brand new things. If i want to be working on things of update level 1, i'll work on only things that i have come up with before but never updated, and update those things. If i'm working on update level 5, then i'll work on only things that have been updated 5 times (well actually 4 times if you dont count the original inception as an update)</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>8:58 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; how to play the snare drum&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; hit it with a stick, pretty much</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>12:46 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; good golly i feel the urge to create but too fixated on the end product rather than the process. help. i cant be a master of every hobby immediately then i burn myself out. ouchie. how does one conquer this conundrum&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it sounds like you have yet to invent yourself into the new king of the avant garde &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 11:28 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Are spheres the perfect 3 dimensional objects?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; possibly. as you can see that doesnt mean they are always 'the best', or even any good. well no surely they're good sometimes &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 10:46 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; why is the math video i uploaded for a class project gaining traction&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; maybe it was good &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 10:23 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; favorite color gradient?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; how about enjoying a series of slightly different colored gradients, gradually &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 9:21 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What do you think happens inside of black holes?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; anything and everything. this is sort of like a book wondering what happens outside the book &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.11.26&amp;nbsp; 9:20 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Did u rub your jeans for the percussion of I'm scared?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i dont think so, but i know i did it for 'airport terminal'</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 12:54 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; whats your favorite song&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbs</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>if any song is any good it ought to be that one, at least while it's on</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>3:09 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Would it be reasonable to call the equals sign ("=") the equator?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it would be great except in english that word already has a strong universal connotation with the 0 degree latitude line on the earth globe. like even if you were not already talking about globes, youre doing math doing math etc then you say 'equator' and immediately everyone now thinks youre talking about globes. the word is already in use for that. Otherwise it could have been a great word for the equals sign in mathematics, for sure</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>3:13 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; think of the weirdest color you can think of&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yellow</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>6:56 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; sometimes figuring out the tooling/processes to do something can be fun, but the problem is you can get distracted for a lifetime of improving on it and never actually get shit done. I've been doing this for 2 years at this point and I seem addicted to it despite clearly noticing the problem. How do i stop being an idito&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it's time to even more honestly weigh the advantages and disadvantages here &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 4:28 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; would you say you like more things than you dislike? or is that impossible to quantify&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; that would be answer B, impossible to quantify. final answer</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 8:42 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; any idea how to start making music if I know no music theory</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>good news, even if you knew how to make music you still wouldnt know &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 7:44 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you have perfect pitch? do you wish you did?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i would want to know your opinion first, of what you think that means and whether you think it's good &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 7:41 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; favorite mathematician?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; euler obviously &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 6:50 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; any hot tips or sweet tricks on maintaining patience?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i will tell you them later &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 5:34 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Where can I get that red bass from your videos&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i'm still using it, but the good news is it's not special, so you'll be able to accomplish just as much (probably more) with another bass. With the added benefit of, just in case anyone were to notice this, you wouldnt appear to be copying me (which probably no one would notice anyway, because it is a fairly generic looking instrument) &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 5:07 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; hi bill, i have a physics issue I came up with that i want your opinion on: imagine a perfect sphere one meter in diameter, made of a nondescript matter with perfect curvature and no substructures (atoms, quarks, molecules, etc). A perfect sphere, as if someone just drag-and-dropped a UV sphere from blender into the real world. What do you think would happen when our real atoms touched this theoretical object? would our atoms be pushed into each-other, undergoing fusion, or something more interesting?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; according to the description it seems to be monkeying with things on a subatomic level, which, at the very least, means i have no idea what would happen, or if the thing would even be visible, or what. but something tells me there is also something not well enough defined about the question. but i assure you i do not know, i am not a physicist &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 4:01 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is the best kind of clock?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; all of them, in due time &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 3:45 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; are we sure potatoes grow underground? Or do they just hide from humans when they hear us approach?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i don't know that much about potatoes &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 2:51 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What's a prank you like to do&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; being born &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 1:16 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Why was 6 afraid of 7?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; because they both became so violently trendy so suddenly that corruption and excess drove them into paranoid jealous rage &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 11:55 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Thoughts on pitch bending on vibraphone? I like how it sounds like "dee-woo".&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; so crazy it just might work &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 9:32 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Why is this page called questions and not questions and answers? The answers are a very important part of the experience&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i suppose i didn't want to spoil that part &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.12.26&amp;nbsp; 8:04 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Thoughts on E major?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; higher than Eb major. lower than F major</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>4:39 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; why is socialization so fricking hard and how can i make it easier&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; maybe you could find a way to pretend it's..... real &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 4:05 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; How committed are you to education?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i'm very serious about educating myself, if that's even possible, and i'm also mindful to educate others when appropriate, BUT that of course can be sand trap of arrogance, because, who am i to assume that i know something that someone else 'doesnt and should' know &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 2:56 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What do you feel are your strengths&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; being weak!!!! &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 2:14 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; should i write down songs that I made and played in my head for 2 years before I forget all of them by going through the trouble of garageband&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes absolutely &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 1:11 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; hey bill how is 2026&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; probably fine, but we MOSTLY dont know yet &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 11:11 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; If you could invent a new number, what would it be and what would you name it?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; let's face it, if i knew what it was then i would have already invented it &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 11:07 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; how often do your song ideas come from dreams?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; at least a couple times a month &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 10:45 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Can you be nostalgic for the present?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes i believe so. and that's definitely a wonderful trick if you can accomplish it &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 8:00 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Why is it called the kick drum if you don't actually kick it yourself&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; close enough, you kick a pedal that kicks it. like when you call someone on the phone, you actually call an operator who calls the person (update! the operater was replaced by a machine! a long time ago actually) &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 6:59 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Favorite time of day?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 6:59 am &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 6:05 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; I need you to know that the Kiwi has the largest egg to body ratio of any bird on Earth.&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; that's very impressive. thanks to you i am very impressed with the Kiwi &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 4:51 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; is the world stupid &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 3:59 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; where would you go if you could teleport&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; anywhere &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 1:38 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Would you say you've become quite an expert on answering questions? A real questionnaire you might say?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 'eer' not 'aire', lets say. 'questionaire' already means 'a list of questions'. -eer is more often used for someone who can do something. engineer, racketeer, actually not sure what a racketeer does, make rackets i suppose</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>5:16 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you think people are born into the world, or born of it, like leaves from a tree?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i'm not sure if i understand the difference &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 4:57 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; I know you've gotten music from your dreams before, but have you ever gotten videos?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes i believe so</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>5:38 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; how did you become the person you now are&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; by being the person i once was</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>9:00 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Does our free will to make choices actually create alternate timelines or are we just too busy living in our crazy world to realize we're too predictable to make any other choice?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i am certainly a believer in the 'many worlds' theory, of infinitely branching timelines at any given moment, and free will is essentially us choosing which one to go on right now. while i also believe that we will probably do all the others EVENTUALLY as it comes back around in infinite million lifetimes. also i think this necessitates the belief that each one will also be chosen infinite times &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 8:55 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; How exactly DOES Believability Bob calculate believability?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; believes everything. bob is extremely gullible &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 8:45 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Do you sometimes stand in your room?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i was going to say no but now that i think about it yes &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 8:36 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Should my friend name their dog Bingo?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; that could cause a lot of chaos, but sure &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 6:53 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; does procrastination imply anticrastination&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no i dont believe so &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 6:51 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; I am the ninth letter of the alphabet.&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; fair play, mate &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 5:50 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; i find it that you use "meme" as a general term for, among other things, what i would call "meme templates" or even "meme template templates". do you think you have a similar subdistinction&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; memes are a meme, that's for sure. and it just so happens that one of the best templates for a meme is in fact the meme template template template template template &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 5:46 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; bill, i've noticed recently that i have been writing too many songs with descending chord progressions. any idea how i can get myself out of this loop?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; make at least one song without any of these things (whatever they may be), and see what's the most fun you can have doing it</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;another way to look at it (and also not the only way), for example, is: in the past, most </title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 8:13 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; favorite philosopher?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; surprise me &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 8:10 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; how many digits of euler's number do you memorize&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i dont know any of it. havent looked into it yet. i would have but i've been busy making music etc for a long time &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 7:25 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; I've always felt banjo is a bit of a subpar instrument. I mean, it produces a unique kind of sound so this fact alone justifies its existence, but to me it always lacked some richness and sexiness that comes from other stringed instruments like guitar. (Side note I just realized - banjo is kinda like a reverse bass. Or maybe ukulele is) &lt;br/&gt;I know it has its use cases and wouldn't want to tell anyone what to play bc who the heck am &lt;br/&gt;What are you thoughts on banjo?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i've used it in probably the majority of my songs. it's incredibly groovy. so in this case i apologize, if you have ever listened to my music, for all the banjo in it &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 6:57 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What is your favourite jazz chord&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; hot take there is no such thing as a 'jazz chord' and also a different chord is favored at each moment of the music &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 6:29 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; have you ever thought of making a full length album?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes but i'd rather just make many many many songs &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 3:24 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what does your average bass fx chain look like? any tips or warnings for people envious of your mixing?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it probably will help a lot to clear the bass frequencies away from the non-bass instruments during times when the full band is playing. single out the instruments that are really doing the low frequency job (bass, kick) and let them have the low end, and keep that mostly out of the other instruments. this can help a lot. and also compressing the bass (not have a lot of loud-soft range) will help usually help. for some reason, wide loud-soft range is usually not too useful on the bass &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 3:07 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; any tips on how to reconcile with something you have to live with forever?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it might be possible to use it to your advantage. ultimately that is the best way to handle these things, if at all possible &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 2:23 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What's the difference between a connoisseur and an aficionado?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; "connaisseur" is from french, meaning expert/judge/taster. "aficionado" is from spanish, it means a fan/enthusiast of something but it also means 'amateur'. The meanings of those 2 words may have merged together a little when used in english, but looking into french and spanish i can see that perhaps the connaisseur may perhaps be a little more high brow than the aficionado &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 1:04 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What are you up to this year? any fun plans?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i dont plan exactly by year, but i have some ridiculous plans for both the near and distant future &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 12:39 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what should i do with my life&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i wouldnt want to spoil the surprise of the different possibilities you'll discover. actually they'd even surprise me because i dont know them &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 12:36 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Do you have this question part of your website to entertain fans or for yourself? Does answering them help with the creative process at all by getting your mind "going"?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i just love reading things in a purple font &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 12:16 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Bill, I hope this is not too personal but I remember the time when you didn't feel comfortable sharing your own food consumption preferences (something I find very respectable and reasonable). Can I ask what made you change your mind on the matter? Thanks. Keep up the great work, you are needed.&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i've generally found it boring and a little unsettling to talk about physical body processes to a wide audience, HOWEVER, going into the AI era this is changing a little because i think being a real-blooded human-ass being is starting to become a more cherished thing to be proud of. like, i actually use toilets, if you can believe that shit &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 11:59 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; If you had to pay a nickel to listen to nickelback would you want a refund after&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it's hard to imagine this situation because in general it is free to listen to nickelback &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 11:06 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; since there is no coloring for "m" in "sumic" on your spotify bio, does that mean your bio on spotify is indeed the word "sumic"&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes but that's just music, spelt casually &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 10:42 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What has been your favorite question asked thus far?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; this one &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.13.26&amp;nbsp; 9:45 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; i love your music, would you ever consider making a full length album?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i always turn out to be more of a song person</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>2:49 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; How do you feel about the word cabbage phonetically? I personally enjoy the sound and texture of it.&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; it's good but not as good as "cribbage" &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 2:37 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is the best substitute for curtains&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; .... shades? &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 1:57 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Is the sun 5 nanometers away?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; from what, nevermind, no i dont think so &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 1:25 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What's your favorite Pok&amp;eacute;mon?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; the.... yellow one &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 1:24 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; sorry if this is a rude question but i suspect you'll answer when the time is right: will people be seeing, hearing and feeling new videos from you soon?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes i believe so &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 1:14 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; can I count on you to live as long as possible.&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; yes i believe so. i'm very serious about my work, which is intimately connected to being alive &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 10:15 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what do i say at the interview to make them want to hire me&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; one classic trick is to ask them questions &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 8:19 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; have you heard of the new instinct-vs-intellect explanation of the human condition and do you think it's probable? basically that our ape ancestors were completely instinctively orientated to love, but that when they developed a conscious mind it clashed with the instincts, causing it to become psychologically upset which is the mad state we still suffer from today and have for eons tried to free ourselves from&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i think that's a bit of storytelling and it's certainly not the only way to look at it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>9:25 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; would you ever not be a princess&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i was going to say yes but now that i think about it no &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 9:20 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is something that is not a pyramid scheme&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; "fair and square" &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 8:50 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Why do we call them cookies if we specifically bake them?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; some sort of language mixeroo. as usual &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 8:35 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; how do i actually make music? i like making fun sound on the piano but i look into making music and its just piles of words i dont understand.. so how do you go from "oh this sounds nice" to a completed song?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; at some point it's worth asking yourself what you feel a completed song should be. Do you feel other songmakers have gotten it right, or deep down do you wish it was a little different? &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 8:13 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what exact date will you release a new song&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; many dates but it will probably be a weekly schedule or something similar &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 4:37 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; oxford sent me a rejection letter yesterday, should I reject their rejection letter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; this could get out of control &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 4:20 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; i just ate some carrots it was about a 6/10 experience wait i lied it was actually 6.5 it was pretty fun&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i'm following along with the story so far &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 4:16 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; wat is mgic to u? as in hw u dfine it&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; magic is a word i sometimes use to describe other things &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 4:10 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; What is your favorite month and why is it the one you choose?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; whatever month it currently is &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 3:44 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you ever think feelings, or feel thoughts?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; now we're talkin &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 3:35 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; &amp;nbsp;How much time does it typically take for you to respond to a question after it is asked?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; let's see, donderdag 15 januari 2026 22:27:13 maybe about 31 hours, for example</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>5:42 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Do you have any interesting tales from the creation of the music and/or video of outside?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; had the chorus/title idea first &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 5:24 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; hey I forgot what my last question was what was it?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; was it &lt;a href="q.php?date=202510280215"target="_blank"&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;&lt;remqq&gt;&lt;/remqq&gt; &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 2:27 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Hello, I just wanted to thank you for something. See, someone I knew recently died of something that almost killed me, and I've been having a horrendous time dealing with all of the things my brain is doing about it. I was feeling exceptionally not OK, went on YT to watch some cat videos to try to calm down, and saw one of your videos in my recommendations. I decided out of curiosity to see which of your videos were released around the time I was sick. And I found out that you posted "if the world doesn't end" right when I was... not quite well yet, but through the dark and experiencing the miracle that I had survived. It helped end a panic attack (so did the cats.) It's so strangely comforting. So I just wanted to thank you. Please keep being weird and amazing. I suppose I need a question here, so... what do you want to do if the world doesn't end?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; make a huge pile of songs that is twice as high and twice as important as all the others before &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 12:18 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; do you like rain?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; in moderation &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 11:20 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; thoughts on raging bureaucracy?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; seems pretty chill &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 9:33 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; I forgot what I was going to say &lt;br/&gt;could you tell me?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; no because you could always change your mind after i predict &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 8:00 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Thoughts on anarchy?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; surprisingly organized &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 6:37 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; How many Christian communions do you think one would have to attend in order to have consumed one entire Jesus?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; sometimes you can get it all in one &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 2:40 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is your operational definition of "near future"&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; i suppose it's all relative &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 1:10 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Ive been playing guitar for a while and ive also recently started playing bass. Im still not too good at guitar even after having played it for a year already, and im new to bass so that's obvious how I'm doing. Have you got ANY good tips for continuing my learning of music in general, or anything specific about those instruments?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; you're going to figure out it all anyway, and it's going to be way more fun than if i tell you the wrong thing at the wrong time &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 12:45 am&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Should I tell my crush that she has the power to break the patterns that torment her?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; sure but it might be hard to convince her that you also wouldn't mind if she broke those patterns without you &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 11:39 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; Who is going to win the super bowl?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; the NFL &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.14.26&amp;nbsp; 9:48 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what if i just made a statement instead of a question&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; so crazy it just might work</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>8:09 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; what is the answer to the ultimate question of life, the universe, and everything?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; a book quote.... which sometimes even overshadows the book it's from &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;dco&gt;1.15.26&amp;nbsp; 8:02 pm&lt;/dco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;qco&gt; the person who said banjo is subpar... what? they've certainly not heard it in the genre, and it can sound quite sad and wistful and profound in the right song. now my question for you: is there an instrument you feel you've underutilised or not used at all but would want to include more?&lt;/qco&gt; &lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; jeans, for sure</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;h3 style="display: inline;"&gt;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>--&gt; &lt;/br&gt; &lt;input type="hidden" name="location" value="question" /&gt; &lt;input type="text" name="website" style="display:none;" /&gt; &lt;input type="button" onclick="submit_question();" name="website" style="display:none;" value="ASK"/&gt; &lt;input type="button" onclick="submit_question();" value="ASK"/&gt;  &lt;/form&gt; &lt;/br&gt;&lt;!--~~~~--&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>.</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>&lt;/qco&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;subanswerwithmoreinline&lt;h3 style="display: inline;"&gt; &lt;qco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>qq</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>&lt;/qco&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;subansw&lt;h3&gt; &lt;qco&gt; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;!--</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;textarea rows="7" cols="47" maxlength="10000" name="question"onkeypress="on_press(event, this)"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ask a question&lt;/br&gt;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;form action="questions.php" method="post" name="ask"&gt;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>}</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>} } //does not refresh the page!! on safari back or reload of page make the question not submitted window.addEventListener('pageshow', function(e) { question_submitted_already = false; document.getElementsByName("question")[0].value = ""; }); &lt;/script&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>// after this many char, enter will work again var CHARACTERS_TO_DISALLOW_ENTER = 100; var question_submitted_already = false; function submit_question() { if (question_submitted_already == false) { question_submitted_already = true; document.forms["ask"].submit(); } } function on_press(e) { var code = (e.keyCode ? e.keyCode : e.which); // check for orientation field on mobile if (!(typeof window.orientation !== "undefined") || (navigator.userAgent.indexOf('IEMobile') !== -1)) { var question = document.getElementsByName("question")[0].value; // if u press enter and no shift, send q if (code == 13 &amp;&amp; !e.shiftKey &amp;&amp; question.length &lt; CHARACTERS_TO_DISALLOW_ENTER) { submit_question(); e.preventDefault();</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;input type="submit" value="i'm feeling randy" style="</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>background-color:black; color: red; font-size:8px; width:85px; "&gt;  &lt;/form&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;h1&gt;ue&lt;font color=#00EE3B&gt;q&lt;/font&gt;stions&lt;/h1&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;/style&gt;</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>&lt;/head&gt; &lt;head&gt;&lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="main.css" media="screen" /&gt; &lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="note.css" media="screen and (max-device-width: 800px)" /&gt; &lt;/head&gt; &lt;meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0,"/&gt; &lt;body&gt; &lt;body style="word-wrap: break-word;"&gt; &lt;/body&gt; &lt;body bgcolor=#323232&gt; &lt;/body&gt; &lt;body text=white&gt; &lt;/body&gt; &lt;body link="#00FF00"&gt; &lt;/body&gt; &lt;body vlink=#67FF79&gt; &lt;/body&gt; &lt;span class="alignright"&gt;&lt;form action="random.php"&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>&lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd"</title><link>https://billwurtz.com/questions/questions.html</link><description>&lt;html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"&gt; &lt;head&gt; &lt;title&gt;questions&lt;/title&gt; &lt;style&gt; dco {color:#E9EC54;} rco {color:#ff6600;} qco {color:#B387FF;} green {color: #00cc00;} blue {color: #5555ff;} white {color: #000000;} lightred {color: #ff6666;} strike {text-decoration:line-through;} red {color: #ff4444;} yellow {color: #ffff00;} lightgreen {color: #b3ffb3;} .alignright { float: right; } .alignleft { float: left; } quotequestion{ margin:20px; padding:5px; display:block; background-color:#444; border: 1px solid black; } quotedco{color:#e9ec54} quoteqco{color:#b387ff} quoteaco{color:#ffffff; font-weight:normal;}</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>